<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
				<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:g="http://base.google.com/ns/1.0">
					<title>Seight Custom Cycling Wear</title>
					<link rel="self" href="http://www.seightcustom.com.au"/>
					<updated>2013-04-01T19:07:07Z</updated>
					<author>
						<name>Seight Custom Cycling Wear</name>
					</author>
					<id>tag:1364807227</id>
				<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Cap]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-cap-test]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The Seight Cap is designed from a soft, lightweight, waterproof, wind repelling, and extremely breathable poly fabric. It has an exceptional ability to soak up sweat and prevent it from running into your eyes. It also dries quickly and its machine washable.  The cap is reinforced with a strong elastic fastener to hold it tightly in place when the wind whips past your ears. It fits under your helmet nicely for an amazing look and a relaxed ride. The cap is fully sublimated, meaning high quality durable prints, while giving you a wide array of different colors to choose from. For a cap only order, our Seight caps come in a package of 15 pieces minimum, and 10 pieces if they are part of a jersey order.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[36]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[24.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/k/180/Seight_Cap__96353_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.6100 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Short Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-short-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Are you  looking for a comfy, reliable, and superior quality jersey at an  economical price? Then the Seight Short Sleeve Jersey is what you need.  Made from pure polyester, and designed with specially engineered quick  drying micro fibre, it&#039;s your optimum solution when it comes to wicking  moisture from the body and keeping you cool.  The  jerseys fabric is UV rated, protecting you from the sun&#039;s harmful rays.  It comes standard with a 3/4 length zipper for regulating air flow when  you&#039;re riding, and also has a waist gripper that holds the edge of your  jersey from rising above your waist. For those who like to carry  multiple items, its 3 pockets will allow you to hold all your cycling  accessories.  Features  - Club and Relaxed Cuts- 3/4 length zipper-Super Light weight- 145 gsm UPF25+ fabric- 3 rear pockets ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Jerseys]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[37]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[79.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/t/669/Seight_Short_Sleeve_Jersey__73839_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Elite Short Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-elite-short-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Outstanding performance, a perfect fit, and extreme comfort; ride like a pro in our Seight Elite Short Sleeve Jersey. Its high performance fabrics perform brilliantly in wicking moisture from the body, while it is also UV rated, protecting you form the sun&#039;s harmful rays. Offering a soft and silky feel, the jersey is made up of two lightweight, stretchable, and breathable fabrics on different panels of the garments.   The short sleeve jersey has three rear pockets which give you easy access to your riding essentials, and the full zipper allows the flow of air, giving you the comfort and fresh air needed throughout your ride. It also has a silicon waist gripper that ensures the hem does not &amp;lsquo;ride up&amp;rsquo; leaving your waist exposed when cycling.   Features  - Pro Race, Club and Relaxed Cuts- Full length zipper- &quot;Natural&quot; sleeves- 145 gsm UPF50+ fabrics- 3 rear pockets ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Jerseys]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[38]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[102.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/f/371/Seight_Elite_Short_Sleeve_Jersey__77210_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Summer Short Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-summer-short-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Perfectly made to suit all your cycling needs throughout the summer, the Seight Summer Short Sleeve Jersey delivers an outstanding performance in wicking moisture from the body. It&amp;rsquo;s made of pure polyester fabrics with specially engineered quick drying microfiber, and is designed to take care of your skin against bacteria infections and protect you from harmful UV rays.  The jersey is light in weight, stretchable with three separate breathable fabrics used on its panels. It even has mesh inserts to allo for better ventilation.The jersey has three rear pockets which give you easy access to your riding essentials. The full zipper allows the flow of air and gives you the comfort and fresh air needed throughout the ride.   Features  - Pro Race, Club and Relaxed Cuts- Full length zipper- Super light weight- Fabrics sourced from both Italy and USA- Mesh style upper back and sleeves- 3 rear pockets ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Jerseys]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[39]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[107.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/n/516/Seight_Summer_Short_Sleeve_Jersey__31704_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Elite Pro Short Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-elite-pro-short-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Are you looking for cycling attire that is unique, elegant and classy? Then, don&amp;rsquo;t go further than the Seight Elite Pro Short Sleeve Jersey. Made from high quality Italian and USA fabrics, this should be the ultimate jersey for anyone that want that extra bit of quality.Like the Aero pro short sleeve jerysey  the power band sleeves heightens joint stability by improving muscle balance. T  With the jersey designed in a way that completely hugs the curves of your body, you will be confident and comfortable, while the seamless power band sleeves will ensure your biceps dont feel like they&#039;re being restricted. The full zipper allows good air ventilation and cools your body when it warms up, and you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be worried of your essentials as the three rear pockets will carry them safely.   Features  - Pro Race and Club Cuts- Full length zipper- Seamless power band sleeves- Fabrics sourced from both Italy and USA (3 different fabrics used on each jersey)- Mesh underams- 3 ...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Jerseys]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[40]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[132.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/r/146/Seight_Elite_Pro_Short_Sleeve_Jersey__22825_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Aero Pro Short Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-aero-pro-short-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The Seight Aero Pro Short Sleeve jersey is our top of the line race jersey, designed from recyclable USA, and Italian made fabrics. It stands second to none in terms of quality and looks. Made from top of the line race produces, the jersey is extremely effective at, well being aerodynamic, whilst wicking moisture from the body and protecting your skin against harmful sun rays. It also has an amazing antibacterial protection system to prevent bad odours.  This multi panel design ensures the jersey is contoured to your body for an aerodynamic yet relaxed fit. It has a full length zipper for easy air circulation and two rear pockets to keep your cycling accessories. The special waist band prevents the edge of your jersey from rising above your waist when cycling, while the power band sleeves heightens joint stability by improving muscle balance.  This cycling jersey is best suited for pro riders planning on a long breakaway!  Features  - Aero cut- Full length zipper- Light weight lycra...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Jerseys]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[41]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[152.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/q/732/Seight_Aero_Pro_Short_Sleeve_Jersey__27952_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.0000 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Winter Long Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-winter-long-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The Seight Winter Long Sleeve Jersey rises above its competitors when it comes to keeping you warm in the freezing cold of winter. Its wide surface area removes moisture from your body quickly to protect your skin against bacterial infections and odour, while the high-tech inner fleece shell works to keep your body warm and dry.   The jerseys breathable panels are made from stretchable fabrics to ensure comfort and maximum movement ability, while remaining lightweight and fast drying. It has three rear pockets located on its back to carry heavy cycling accessories, and the full length zipper comes in handy if you need to vent a bit of heat.  Features  - 280 gsm 100% polyester- Full length zipper- Designed with specially-engineered quick-drying microfiber; - Naturally soft, lightweight, stretchable, breathable and comfortable; - Sweat-expelling, odor and bacteria resistant;  - Keeps the wearer dry, cool and fresh.        ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Jerseys]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[43]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[117.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/w/010/Seight_Winter_Long_Sleeve_Jersey__43071_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.2900 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Elite Sleeveless Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-elite-sleeveless-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Cutting edge technology and modern design have been well demonstrated by the Seight Elite Sleeveless Jersey. It performs brilliantly in moisture wicking and is also UV rated to protect your body against harmful sun rays. Its panels give this jersey a perfect fit on your body and also improve air flow to keep you cool.  The jersey is made from 100% polyester with specially designed quick drying micro fibre. It is stretchable to enhance flexibility and comfort when cycling, and  has a 3/4 zipper which lets in fresh air, finished with a silicon waist gripper to keep the jersey in its position. It also has 3 deep rear-pockets give you easy access to your riding accessories.   Features  - UV protective fabric- Naturally soft, lightweight, stretchable and breathable- 145 gsm UPF 50+ fabric- YKK zipper        ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Jerseys]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[44]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[87.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/h/571/Seight_Elite_Sleeveless_Jersey__98836_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.3200 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Bib Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-bib-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[If you are looking for a great entry-level bib shorts, the Seight Bib Shorts are exactly what you need. They are a modern and comfy cycling apparel that gives you great value for your money, and are well designed to fit both men and women riders.  Standard stitching of these bib shorts ensures reduced sewing seams and a smooth feel, while the 6+ panel design conforms well to your body when you bend over in a cycling position. Made with a polyester and lycra sublimated panel, moisture wicking and breathability are enhanced to reduce the chances of chafing. The high density chamois lining is antibacterial, while the silicon leg gripper prevents the shorts from riding up.  Features  - Sublimated Panel: POLY-LYCRA&amp;trade; 220 gsm  - Unsublimated Chamois Panel: NYLON-LYCRA&amp;trade; 220 gsm  - Elastic Waistband- Silicon Gel Chamois - Elite 6 thread FLATLOCK stitching ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shorts &amp; Bib Shorts]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[45]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[94.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/z/293/Seight_Bib_Shorts__38733_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.3600 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Elite Bib Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-elite-bib-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Are you a long distance rider? Then the Seight Elite Bib Shorts are perfect for you. They are made with high quality lycra fabrics to ensure breathability and enhanced comfort. Its Flatlock style stitching produces gentle seams resulting to smooth cycling, and the 8+ panels delivers a perfect fit when you bend over in a cycling posture.   The seamless super high-tech chamois is made in a way that decreases friction between your body and the saddle, and the silicon leg grippers hold the shorts in place for an increased level of comfort. The&amp;nbsp; multi structure levels relieve the pressure points between your body and your bike saddle, while the fabrics and foams are anatomically combined to support your body and reduce muscle fatigue. These chamois features make Seight Elite Bib Shorts the most comfortable cycling item available in Australia.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shorts &amp; Bib Shorts]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[46]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[131.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/h/735/Seight_Elite_Bib_Shorts__06114_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.3900 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Elite Winter Bib Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-elite-winter-bib-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The  Seight Elite Winter Bib Shorts enhance the comfort on your ride, plain and simple.  It&amp;rsquo;s designed with sublimated Fleece LYCRA fabric, which fits  perfectly like a second skin to keep your body dry and warm. The modern  multi-level chamois is designed with the Flatlock stitching technique to  deliver strong, durable, and low profile seams. It has an anatomical  shape which provides you with comfort at a high level when cycling.  &amp;nbsp;  Features  - 250 gsm Fleece LYCRA- Elite 3D Italian Chamois - Elite 6 thread FLATLOCK style stitching]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shorts &amp; Bib Shorts]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[47]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[135.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/v/487/Seight_Winter_Bib_Shorts__40592_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.4300 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Elite Pro Bib Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-elite-pro-bib-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Perfect, immaculate, and incredible - is what best describes the Seight Elite Bib Shorts. It is indeed the top pro bib shorts ever made, bar none! The sublimated panel is made with 240gsm Lycra from Italy, while the unsublimated panel is 225gsm, which means maximum quality and breathability during extreme physical workouts.   The Italian made chamois has a number of features, such as being seamless, an anatomical shape, and multi-level structures for increased comfort and protection. Its elite thread Flatlock stitching method gives this short an appealing look and a soft feeling on the skin, and the power band leg gripper keeps the bib shorts in place.   Features  - Sublimated Panel: Italian LYCRA&amp;trade; 240 gsm  - Unsublimated Chamois Panel: Italian LYCRA&amp;trade; 225 gsm  - Elite 3D Italian Chamois  - Elite 6 thread FLATLOCK stitching- Powe Band leg gripper]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shorts &amp; Bib Shorts]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[48]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[151.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/o/916/Seight_Elite_Pro_Bib_Shorts__02008_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.4600 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Winter Elite Pro Bib Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-winter-elite-pro-bib-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[We refer to them as Seight Winter Elite Pro Bib Shorts, but you may call them the supreme comfort. Made from multi-panel fleece Lycra from Italy,  these custom bib shorts are very breathable and leave no room for bacteria propagation whilst keeping you warm on those early morning wintery rides. It has a different density throughout the chamois to give you comfort in all of your pedalling positions.  These elite winter bib shorts are made with a 6 thread Flatlock stitching technique for low profile seams to minimise the possibility of chafing, and giving a clean and smooth finish. The power band grippers ensure the bib shorts remain firmly in place at all times, and offers the ultimate comfort and flexibility whether competing in a race or riding for leisure.  Features  - Sublimated Panel: Italian Super Roubaix Gavia&amp;trade; 250 gsm  - Unsublimated Chamois Panel: Italian Super Roubaix Lombardia&amp;trade; 250 gsm  - Elite 3D Italian Chamois  - Elite 6 thread FLATLOCK stitching- Powe Band ...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shorts &amp; Bib Shorts]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[49]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[155.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/g/554/Seight_Winter_Elite_Pro_Bib_Shorts__13174_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.4600 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The Seight Shorts are anatomically designed for the ultimate comfort whilst riding. Made with multi-panelled Lycra,  these shorts are very breathable and leave no room for bacteria propagation. It has a different density throughout the chamois to give you comfort in all of your pedalling positions.   The waistband ensures the shorts remain firmly in place at all times, and offers the ultimate comfort and flexibility whether competing in a race or riding for leisure.  Features  - Sublimated Panel: POLY-LYCRA&amp;trade; 220 gsm  - Unsublimated Chamois Panel: NYLON-LYCRA&amp;trade; 220 gsm  - Elastic Waistband- Silicon Gel Chamois - Elite 6 thread FLATLOCK stitching ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shorts &amp; Bib Shorts]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[50]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[94.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/x/661/Seight_Shorts__50042_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.5000 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Elite Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-elite-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Thinking of high performance, comfortable and yet durable cycling shorts? Look no further than the Seight Elite Shorts. This magnificent design is made using Italian sublimated Miti Shield Lycra, which ensures good perspiration absorption, and provides a healthy and comfortable ride. The pad has a high varying density to provide you with comfort by acting as shock absorbers in the perinea area.   The Elite Shorts are anatomical shaped to give a perfect fit and an easy time through out the ride. They are designed with 6 thread Flatlock stitching technology that eliminates chafing, and feature an elastic and flexible waist band which holds the shorts tightly in their position, and prevents body exposure.   Features  - Sublimated Panel: POLY-LYCRA&amp;trade; 220 gsm  - Unsublimated Chamois Panel: NYLON-LYCRA&amp;trade; 220 gsm  - Elite 3D Italian Chamois  - Elite 6 thread FLATLOCK style stitching]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shorts &amp; Bib Shorts]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[51]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[112.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/n/303/Seight_Elite_Shorts__40691_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.5400 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Elite Winter Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-elite-winter-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The Seight Winter Shorts enhance the comfort on your ride, plain and simple. It&amp;rsquo;s designed with sublimated Fleece LYCRA, which fits perfectly like a second skin to keep your body dry and warm. The modern multi-level chamois is designed with the Flatlock stitching technique to deliver strong, durable, and low profile seams. It has an anatomical shape which provides you with comfort at a high level when biking.  The waist band offers relaxation and flexibility in your biking position and ensure the shorts stay in position.  Features  - 250 gsm Fleece LYCRA- Elite 3D Italian Chamois - Elite 6 thread FLATLOCK style stitching]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shorts &amp; Bib Shorts]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[52]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[116.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/h/198/Seight_Winter_Shorts__16787_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.5700 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom 3/4 Elite Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-34-elite-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[  These Seight 3/4 Elite Shorts  are made with 240gsm sublimated Lycra fabric for superb performance,  easy moisture transfer and great comfort. They are equipped with a multi  level unsublimated chamois that is anatomically shaped to enhance  comfort, and  efficiently manages moisture and gives you optimum  flexibility.   Its fabrics and forms are perfectly  combined, and this ensures you are fully supported when you are on the  saddle. These 3/4 Elite Shorts have an elastic waistband to ensure your shorts will nver fall down&amp;nbsp; It is designed with flatlock technique to guarantee a smooth and  strong ride.   Features  - Sublimated Panel: POLY-LYCRA&amp;trade; 220 gsm  - Unsublimated Chamois Panel: NYLON-LYCRA&amp;trade; 220 gsm  - Elite 3D Italian Chamois  - Elite 6 thread FLATLOCK stitching - 3/4 length legs  ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shorts &amp; Bib Shorts]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[53]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[106.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/d/009/Seight_3-4_Elite_Shorts__05143_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.6100 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom 3/4 Elite Bib Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-34-elite-bib-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[These Seight 3/4 Elite Bib Shorts are made with 240gsm sublimated Lycra fabric for superb performance, easy moisture transfer and great comfort. They are equipped with a multi level unsublimated chamois that is anatomically shaped to enhance comfort, and  efficiently manages moisture and gives you optimum flexibility.   Its fabrics and forms are perfectly combined, and this ensures you are fully supported when you are on the saddle. It is designed with flatlock technique to guarantee a smooth and strong ride.  Features  - Sublimated Panel: POLY-LYCRA&amp;trade; 220 gsm  - Unsublimated Chamois Panel: NYLON-LYCRA&amp;trade; 220 gsm  - Elite 3D Italian Chamois  - Elite 6 thread FLATLOCK style stitching]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shorts &amp; Bib Shorts]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[54]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[122.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/c/774/Seight_3-4_Elite_Bib_Shorts__65443_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.6400 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom 3/4 Elite Winter Bib Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-34-elite-winter-bib-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Are you longing for a warm winter ride? The Seight 3/4 Winter Bib Shorts are what you should have in mind. They are designed with fleecy lycra fabrics to give your body maximum protection from the cold. The chamois is anatomically shaped to fit perfectly and support your body on your ride.  These 3/4 shorts have a thermal fabric lining to keep you warm, and provide excellent performance in moisture wicking to keep the body dry. These 3/4 shorts are made with flatlock stitching method that give them appealing look and gentle feeling against your skin.  Features   - 250 gsm Fleece LYCRA- Elite 3D Italian Chamois - Elite 6 thread FLATLOCK stitching- 3/4 length legs]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shorts &amp; Bib Shorts]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[55]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[127.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/o/671/Seight_3-4_Winter_Bib_Shorts__42093_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.6800 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Full Length Elite Tights]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-full-length-elite-tights]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[With a material that fits perfectly like a second skin, a chamois that provides exceptional comfort and support, Seight Full Length Elite Tights are simply the best on the market. They are made with only the the best Italian lycra. Utilising fatlock stitching technology to guarantee flexibility, durability and comfort you are ensured suburb comfort and guaranteed an enjoyable cycling experience.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shorts &amp; Bib Shorts]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[56]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[131.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/d/388/Seight_Full_Length_Elite_Tights__97907_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.7100 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Full Length Elite Bib Tights]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-full-length-elite-bib-tights]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Seight Full Length Elite Bib Tights are called Elite for a very good reason. They are designed with highly functional material and contain an anatomically shaped chamois for maximum performance and comfort. The fabric easily transfers moisture and regulates temperature for a cool ride whilst being flexible and durable with a soft silky feel.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shorts &amp; Bib Shorts]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[57]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[150.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/c/111/Seight_Full_Length_Elite_Bib_Tights__99372_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.7500 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Full Length Winter Bib Tights]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-full-length-winter-bib-tights]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Heading out for a ride in winter may seem like the wrong idea, however the only that can really be wrong is to be wearing the wrong clothes on your ride. Wearing the Seight Full Length Winter Bib Tights is definitely the right idea in winter, as our high performing Italian Lycra&amp;nbsp; fleecefabric gives you an absolute fit, flexibility and warmth for maximum comfort during winter riding conditions.   &amp;nbsp;  The bib tights chamois has excellent thermal regulation and is anatomically shaped for the ultimate support when cycling. They are stitched using flatlock method to avoid chafing and enhance durability.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Shorts &amp; Bib Shorts]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[58]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[155.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/l/182/Seight_Full_Length_Winter_Bib_Tights__83490_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.7900 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Short Sleeve Skin Suit]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-short-sleeve-skin-suit]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Each detail of the Seight Short Sleeve  Skin Suit has been meticulously observed to create a garment which  delivers a superior cycling experience. It is constructed using top end  Lycra fabrics which wick moisture efficiently, and fits perfectly on  your body and wont flap in the wind whilst riding.   It is designed with side and back  panels that improve breathability and comfort.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Skinsuits]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[59]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[140.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/u/448/Seight_Short_Sleeve_Skin_Suit__30920_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.8200 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Short Sleeve Speed Skin Suit]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-short-sleeve-speed-skin-suit]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Look &amp;amp; feel like a pro rider in the Seight Short Sleeve Speed Skin Suit. It&amp;rsquo;s designed with aerodynamic lycras to ensure not a millisecond is lost. Both legs and arms are powered by proprietary power band sleeves. This design is a perfect blend of  aerodynamics, ergonomic fit and an anatomical shape for a totally  efficient cycling experience. &amp;nbsp;   Every panel is assembled using Flatlock  stitching technology for appealing and quality apparel. The proprietary  power band ensures your apparel stays in its destined position  comfortably, and most importantly allows you to ride at maximum speed.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Skinsuits]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[60]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[210.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/x/157/Seight_Short_Sleeve_Speed_Skin_Suit__54262_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.8600 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Long Sleeve Skin Suit]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-long-sleeve-skin-suit]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Each detail of the Seight Long Sleeve Skin Suit has been meticulously observed to create a garment which delivers a superior cycling experience. It is constructed using top end Lycra fabrics which wick moisture efficiently, and fits perfectly on your body and wont flap in the wind whilst riding. ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Skinsuits]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[61]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[150.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/w/328/Seight_Long_Sleeve_Skin_Suit__24436_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.8900 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Long Sleeve Speed Skin Suit]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-long-sleeve-speed-skin-suit]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Made with aerodynamic lycra fabric, a high performing chamois, and power band grippers, the Seight Long Sleeve Speed Skin Suit conveys all your energy to the pedals for magnificent speed and efficiency. This design is a perfect blend of aerodynamics, ergonomic fit and an anatomical shape for a totally efficient cycling experience.   Every panel is assembled using Flatlock stitching technology for appealing and quality apparel. The proprietary power bandr ensures your apparel stays in its destined position comfortably, and most importantly allows you to ride at maximum speed.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Skinsuits]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[62]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[225.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/j/156/Seight_Long_Sleeve_Speed_Skin_Suit__08723_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.9300 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Wind Vest]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-water-resistant-vest]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[When the climate is at its worst, the Seight windVest is at its best. They are made from wind and water resistant polyester fabrics to enhance comfort and performance when you are riding. The vest is lightweight and breathable for an outstanding cycling experience, and has a mesh that regulates temperature for maximum comfort.  These vests are amazingly packable, so they can be easily scrunched into the rear pockets when the sun peaks out again. Its graphics are sublimated for high quality prints and keep the fabric breathable. They really come in handy during those freakish weather condition which always seem to change from sunshine to rain when you least expect it. ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Vests &amp; Jackets]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[68]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[81.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/p/468/Seight_Water_Resistant_Vest__79122_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.1400 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Thermal Vest]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-thermal-vest]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[For freezing or moderately cold weather conditions, look no further than Seight Thermal Vest. It&amp;rsquo;s designed with 3 layers of wind and water resistant panels that incorporates a 350gsm fleece shell and high performing surface fabrics. The fabric is sublimated to give durable HD graphics and a breathable apparel.  The vest has an oversized semi-locking zipper for efficient air ventilation and to keep you warm and dry when riding. This zipper is also compatible with gloves to increase comfort. The Seight Thermal Vest is designed using cover stitch for durable, flexible, and low profile seams, and  it has a silicon gripper to keep the vest in its place for maximum comfort when riding. It also features 3 optional deep rear pockets to keep the riding essentials such as tools and grub.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Vests &amp; Jackets]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[70]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[120.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/i/989/Seight_Thermal_Vest__90426_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.2100 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Water Resistant Jacket]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-water-resistant-jacket]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[With wind and water resistance, a sleek look and comfy feeling, our Seight Water Resistant Jackets are specifically designed for high performance and protection from wet weather conditions.   This jacket is designed to fight wind, chilly air, and water when pedalling. It has optional zippered rear pockets to provide easy access to your riding accessories, and has a perfect contour to improve mobility in all cycling positions. This jacket is also made with a silicon waistband, so it wont ride up your body whilst cycling.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Vests &amp; Jackets]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[71]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[82.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/h/095/Seight_Water_Resistant_Jacket__10195_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.2500 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Thermal Jacket]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-thermal-jacket]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Comfortable, warm, and economical; what else is there to look for in a cycling jacket.  The jackets fabric is water and wind resistant to keep you warm and provide moisture wicking for a warm and dry body. The jacket is made with 3 windproof fabric layers which incorporate Roubaix fleece, as well as a&amp;nbsp; large collar. It is stitched using a cover stitch technique for durable and elegant seams.   The jacket is equipped with a full windproof zipper for protection against the cold weather, while providing efficient air ventilation. It features an elastic gripper to prevent your jacket from flying up when cycling, and has 3 optional spacious rear pockets to stash your riding gear. It&amp;rsquo;s digitally printed to give long lasting and quality graphics. Seight thermal jacket has all it takes to beat the cold weather.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Vests &amp; Jackets]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[73]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[175.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/e/356/Seight_Thermal_Jacket__29174_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.3200 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Summer Arm Warmers]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-summer-arm-warmers]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Keep your arms cool and dry by wicking moisture from the skin using our Seight Summer Arm Warmers.This warmer is contoured with your arm to increase comfort, flexibility, and overall performance. These warmers have lightweight lycra fabrics for spectacular comfort and high performance in moisture wicking. The durable silicon gripper keeps these arm warmers in position, and the fabric is fully sublimated to improve breathability and a magnificent finish.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[74]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[33.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/n/240/Seight_Summer_Arm_Warmers__74107_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.3600 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Winter Arm Warmers]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-winter-arm-warmers]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Transform all your short sleeve cycling jerseys into full body coverage with our Seight Winter Arm Warmers. These arm warmers are made using full motion flexible fabrics, fleece lining and elastic grippers that equipe you for those cold rides.  &amp;nbsp;They are anatomically shaped to enhance comfort and flexibility when you are on the saddle. Its silicon made grippers are very durable and act brilliantly in preventing the arm warmers from sliding down. They are digital printed to provide a long lasting and high definition fabric.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[75]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[36.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/k/905/Seight_Winter_Arm_Warmers__97192_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.3900 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Summer Leg Warmers]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-summer-leg-warmers]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Stay warm and while supporting your muscles with Seight Summer Leg Warmers. They provide an anatomical fit, have great moisture wicking properties, and are ergonomically shaped to enhance comfort and efficiency. These leg warmers are lightweight and are perfect for those nippy spring mornings.  The leg warmers have silicon made grippers that are responsible for holding the leg warmers in position while riding. They are digital printed to ensure the fabric remains breathable and flexible.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[76]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[46.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/f/937/Seight_Summer_Leg_Warmers__48079_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.4300 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Winter Leg Warmers]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-winter-leg-warmers]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Increase your legs warmth while wearing your best cycling shorts. Seight Winter Leg Warmers uses high quality Roubaix fabrics for exceptional wind protection without excluding moisture management and breathability. They have a fleece lining to keep you warm during cold rides. They are anatomically shaped to enhance comfort and increase riding performance.  The durable elastic gripper ensures the warmer is tightly attached to your body, to minimize contact of the cold breeze with your skin and increase comfort. They are sublimated to guarantee quality graphics and breathable fabric.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[77]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[49.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/e/208/Seight_Winter_Leg_Warmers__77149_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.4600 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Summer Knee Warmers]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-summer-knee-warmers]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Seight Summer Knee Warmers are the ultimate essential item for long distance rides in changing temperatures. Not to warm, but not too cold, they are perfect for that spring morning with just a bit of nip.The Flatlock stitching technology offers low profile, durable and attractive seams. Silicon grippers provide further comfort and prevent chafing by keeping the warmers in place. These warmers are anatomically shaped for a perfect fit.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[78]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[36.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/j/012/Seight_Summer_Knee_Warmers__19313_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.5000 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Winter Knee Warmers]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-winter-knee-warmers]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Riding in winter is more comfortable than ever, thanks to our Seight Winter Knee Warmers. They are made from Roubaix fabrics for a warm, cosy and gentle feeling on your skin. This fabric provides great moisture management, and improved flexibility for a greater riding cycling experience. They have a thermal fleece lining to increase warmth and comfort.  The knee warmers are made using the Flatlock seams that are sewn in matching threads for long lasting and attractive seams. The silicon gripper holds these warmers in place to assure they won&amp;rsquo;t give you a hard time when cycling.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[79]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[39.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/v/972/Seight_Winter_Knee_Warmers__61884_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.5400 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Socks]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-socks]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Our Seight Socks fabrics perform brilliantly in moisture management and feet cooling. It&amp;rsquo;s made from Coolmax fabrics to enhance breathability and moisture transfer for cool and dry feet. With the moisture being drawn away from your fret, this thermal fabric does a great job at eliminating odour. These socks are anatomically shaped for a perfect fit, and are stitched using advanced technology for durable seamless stitching to prevent chafing.  &amp;nbsp;]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[80]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[11.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/s/348/Seight_Socks__62931_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.5700 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Bandana]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-bandana]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The Seight Bandana keeps your head cool and dry regardless of how hot it gets. Moisture managing and highly breathable fabrics send sweat away from your brow for a better riding experience at any temperature. This fabric wicks moisture and transfers it to the outer layers for fast evaporation. These cost effective bandanas are anatomically shaped for the ultimate comfort and to fit well under your helmet.  &amp;nbsp;]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[81]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[21.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/l/130/Seight_Bandana__27311_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.6400 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Summer Gloves]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-summer-gloves]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Hyper ventilated, ultra-light and close fitting, our comfortable Seight Summer Gloves are all a pro rider needs to emerge victorious. They are made of highly breathable lycra fabric that is both light in weight and chaff-free for a cool and comfy feeling. The palm has the perfect contour for a tight fit on the handlebar and also acts as a shock absorber from the riding vibrations.The insulated polyester lycra contains highly absorbent microfibers for quick drying and effective moisture transfer.   This high performing glove has an excellent air ventilation system for maximum air flow. The anatomically shaped inner padding sets the gloves in the hands perfectly for ultimate support, while the optional velcro wrist closure ensures these Seight gloves have a secure fit. They are fully sublimated for durable and breathable High Definition prints. You can choose your preferred colours from our wide range of summer gloves varieties.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[82]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[41.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/g/009/Seight_Summer_Gloves__50550_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.6800 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Winter Gloves]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-winter-gloves]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[This classic full-finger glove is designed for cycling in the grip of luxury. Seight Winter Gloves provide you with maximum dexterity for cycling and racing in extreme weather conditions. They are made with 3 layers to give you flexibility and direct connection with the handlebar, with the outer membrane being waterproof and wind resistant for full protection in cold and wet conditions.   Inside the glove, the X-Static layer protects your skin from bacterial infections caused by moisture, while the fleece lining offers high performance in wicking moisture as well as a soft feeling against your skin. The palm is made for a complete fit around the handlebar and enhances shock absorption from cycling vibrations. These gloves are fully customizable to your design.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[83]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[55.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/z/562/Seight_Winter_Gloves__17793_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.7100 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom TT Overshoes]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-tt-overshoes]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Seight TT Overshoes are perfect shoe covers for racing. Using a stretchable high-tech lycra fabric which facilitates airflow and accelerates its movement during a time trial cycling exercise. This fabric is lightweight and aerodynamic, while the cleat and heel holes are well stitched using flat-lock technology, which increases the overshoe service life while its cuff holds them tightly in the right position.  &amp;nbsp;]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[84]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[45.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/f/661/Seight_TT_Overshoes__81669_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.7500 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Winter Overshoes]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-winter-overshoes]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The Seight Winter Overshoes feature a contemporary design to take care of your feet and keep your bike footwear in great shape in the harshest of winters. Everyone wants to protect their feet from the cold during winter with the right pair of overshoes, and our Winter Overshoes do the job well under the  Seight long-lasting, stretchable, warm, water and wind resistant fabrics.  They are anti-bacterial and lightweight with stitched seams that prevent water leakage, cold and wetness from getting into your shoes. It&amp;rsquo;s fabric is reflective for visibility of the rider with a firm durable YKK zipper. It also has reinforcement on the nose and between the zippers, and the sole. The adjustable velcro rubber strap makes this pairs of overshoes a secure fit for the avid road rider, making them the perfect cycling companion in winter.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[85]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[55.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/n/184/Seight_Winter_Overshoes__62237_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Waterproof Overshoes]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-waterproof-overshoes]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The Seight Waterproof Overshoes are lightweight, breathable and a reflective secure fit for wet weather. With advanced aerodynamic features, they represent an excellent investment in both comfort and keeping your feet warm and dry. Made from a water repellent, polyurethane-coated fabric and constructed with sealed seams and a gripper ankle to close it, they will protect your cycling footwear by being able to withstand extreme erratic weather conditions.  The overshoes are designed with reflective prints to optimize visibility when cycling, and a velcro strap for a perfect secure fit. It&amp;rsquo;s sole is reinforced for a long life span while the zip is adjustable to fit nicely over your footwear. No doubt you&amp;rsquo;ll love this to be your preferred commuting companion. Suitable for long bike rides, the Seight waterproof overshoes are definitely worth investing in.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Accessories]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[86]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[60.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.8200 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Tri Suit]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-tri-suit]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The Seight Tri Suit is hard to beat. Made with input from pro triathletes, it an indispensable part of the racers gear drawer. It is made of supremely lightweight lycra, with multi direction stretch for support and total compression. This tri suit has high moisture wicking capabilities and an exceptionally quick drying process. The elastic ability of the fabric provides freedom of movement while also optimising the aerodynamics.   The tri suits wings are designed with a moisture wicking and buoyancy regulating fabric to improve position in the water, while the panels are made to compress and slow down muscle oscillation in order to conserve energy, reduce fatigue and enhance blood circulation. No leg grippers and well stitched flat-lock seams ideally to eliminate abrasion and increase riders comfort. It has an anatomically designed low profile chamois pad that encourages moisture transfer and supports the rider for the ultimate performance, whilst still being comdortable on the run.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Tri &amp; Run]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[87]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[185.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/v/100/Seight_Tri-Suit__33208_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.8600 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Run Singlet]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-run-singlet]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Our Seight Run Singlet is meticulously designed, inexpensive,UV protective, sweat-expelling, snug, soft and cosy. It is made of soft compressed moisture wicking polyester fabrics, which is anti-bacterial and odour-free. It&amp;rsquo;s air wicking feature allows it to dry quickly, while the side panels improve the singlet moisture management.   The singlets properties make it the best fitting for running, gym workouts, or casual exercise during summer. Its light weight and breathability make it ideal for a long, hot and humid racing environment. The fabric is neatly stitched and chafe-free, and allows full digital sublimation to yield high quality prints, plus can be customized according to your designs and specifications.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Tri &amp; Run]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[88]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[65.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/d/506/Seight_Run_Singlet__41659_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.8900 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Run Top]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-run-top]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Soft, excellent performance, snug fit and comfy to wear are the features of our Seight Run Top. It is manufactured using superb quality fabrics, and specially engineered to yield optimal flexibility and movement. It is light in weight and possesses a high elasticity degree. The flat lock seam construction decreases friction against the body, consequently diminishing the chances of chafing.   It&amp;rsquo;s fabric is exceptional in wicking moisture away from the body and letting fresh air in, keeping the wearer odour-free while the mesh ensures breathability. The run top is exquisitely made to hug the curves of your body for a perfect non-slip fit, thus giving unrestricted movement. The fabric is also protective against harmful UV rays from the sun.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Tri &amp; Run]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[89]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[65.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/i/948/Seight_Run_Top__84891_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.9300 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Mussette Bag]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-mussette-bag]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Musettes are bags used for stuffing goodies and handing them over to racing cyclists to help keep them fuelled up throughout the ride. Filled with food and drinks, pro cyclists grab them when racing and fling them over their head to settle on their back. It&amp;rsquo;s made of total absorbent fabric and is sweat resilient. Our mussette bags are ideal for cyclists as they are lightweight and water resistant, and are also perfect for stuffing items during shopping. It is easily foldable into your pocket, and can be removed at a later stage to carry your belongings.   This bag is fully sublimated. It has a small velcro closure and large loop strap to enable the cyclist to place it comfortably on the shoulders while cycling, and its design gives you easy access to all of the items it contains whilst cycling. ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Casual Wear]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[90]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[30.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/a/688/Seight_Musette_Bag__01992_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[2.0000 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Tech Polo Shirt]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-tech-polo-shirt]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[You will in no doubt fall in love with our intricately designed polyester Seight Tech polo shirt. Made using a fast wicking fabric, it&amp;rsquo;s resilient to odour causing bacteria and allows moisture management. The fabric feels good to the skin, making it a relaxed, comfortable fit. It can be customized as per individual specifications.   Th whole shirt can be fully sublimated with images, logos or designs of your choice. Creative distinct artwork is done exclusively on every polo shirt and every size for high definition prints. It has the choice of a front zipper or 3 buttons on the front, with excellent prices on both. This jersey has a high tear strength that guarantees you the value of your money.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Casual Wear]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[91]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[68.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/b/470/Seight_Tech_Polo_Shirt__16441_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[2.0400 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom T Shirt]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-t-shirt]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[You will definitely love the soft, comfy feel of these t-shirts. It is manufactured using the same high quality materials as our cycling jerseys.  The printing is excellent and the art work is greatly designed with creativity to surpass the client&amp;rsquo;s expectations. The t-shirts are light weight and fits well on all individuals, and are long lasting due to the double needle-stitched sleeve hem and bottom. The colour prints are also fade resistant.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Casual Wear]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[92]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[50.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/x/260/Seight_T_Shirt__52528_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[2.0700 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Casual Winter Jacket]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-casual-winter-jacket]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[This jacket is a cool contemporary winter casual wear item It&amp;rsquo;s made using premium quality fabric and cutting-edge technology to provide warmth and relaxation in the cold climate. The fabric is made of a multi layer wind repellant membrane with 350gsm thermal, windproof and waterproof fleeced fabric.   This jacket can be fully sublimated.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Casual Wear]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[93]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[120.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/b/372/Seight_Casual_Winter_Jacket__31203_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[2.1400 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Casual Winter Vest]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-casual-winter-vest]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[This casual winter vest will provide a great fit, it&amp;rsquo;s made of a multi layer wind repellent membrane with 350 gsm thermal, windproof and waterproof fleeced fabric. The stand-up collar prevents chaffing and offers the desired comfort.  The vest is elegantly stitched to eliminate binding and pinching, giving you the ultimate wear comfort. It&amp;rsquo;s completed with pockets in the front to keep your hands nice and warm. High definition graphics keep it very much on trend and give it an eye-catching appearance.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Casual Wear]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[94]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[105.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/q/174/Seight_Casual_Winter_Vest__03351_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[2.1800 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Elite Long Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/seight-custom-elite-long-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Nothing provides you with protection and comfort when you are out for a ride like the Seight Elite Long Sleeve Jersey. Its wide surface area removes moisture from your body quickly to protect your skin against bacterial infections and odour. The high tech fibre fabric ensures complete air circulation for a cool and dry body.The jersey is UV rated to protect your skin and the jersey from the harmful radiation from the sun. Its breathable panels are made from 2 stretchable fabrics to ensure comfort and maximum movement ability, while remaining lightweight and fast drying. It has three rear pockets located on its back to carry heavy cycling accessories, and the full length zipper comes in handy when venting heat.      Features  - UV protective fabric- Naturally soft, lightweight, stretchable and breathable- 145 gsm UPF 50+ fabric- YKK zipper        ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Jerseys]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[98]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[113.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/j/839/Seight_Elite_Long_Sleeve_Jersey__45719_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[FlexorCranks Winter/Thermal Jacket]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/flexorcranks-winterthermal-jacket]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Comfortable, ultimate performance, warm, economical&amp;mdash;what else is there to look for in a cycling jacket, our thermal jacket has all it takes to beat the cold weather. Its fabric is water and wind resistant to keep you warm and moisture wicking for warm and dry body. The jacket is made of three fabricslayer which incorporate Roubaix fleece, as well as a large collar. It is stitched using cover stitch technique for durable and elegant seams.   &amp;nbsp;It is equipped with a full windproof zipper for protection against cold weather and efficient air ventilation. It has an elastic gripper to prevent your jacket from riding up when cycling. This jacket has 3 spacious rear pockets to stash your riding gear. It&amp;rsquo;s digitally printed to give long lasting and quality graphics.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[FlexorCranks]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[100]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[130.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/g/003/Seoght-FlexorCranks_Long_Sleeve_Jersey_CHROME_210212__20648_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.3200 cm]]></g:width>
	<g:shipping><g:price><![CDATA[0]]></g:price></g:shipping>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[FlexorCranks  Elite Short Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/flexorcranks-elite-short-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Outstanding performance, perfect fit, and comfort, ride like a pro in our Elite Short Sleeve Jersey. Its high performance fabrics perform brilliantly in wicking moisture from the body. Its fabric is UV rated, protecting you form the sun&#039;s harmful rays.  Offering a soft and silky feel, it&amp;rsquo;s made up of two lightweight, stretchable, and breathable fabrics on different panels of the garments. It has three rear pockets which give you easy access to your riding essentials. The full zipper allows the flow of air, giving you the comfort and fresh air needed throughout your ride. It has a silicon waist gripper that ensures the hem does not &amp;lsquo;ride up&amp;rsquo; leaving your waist exposed when cycling.   This jersey comes in the following varieties:  &amp;bull; Men&amp;rsquo;s Pro Race, Club and Casual Cut  &amp;bull; Women&amp;rsquo;s Pro Race and Club Cut]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[FlexorCranks]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[101]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[97.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/q/166/Seight-FlexorCranks_Short_Sleeve_Jersey_CHROME_210212__89348_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:shipping><g:price><![CDATA[0]]></g:price></g:shipping>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[FlexorCranks Winter Arm Warmers]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/flexorcranks-winter-arm-warmers]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Type a description for this product here...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[FlexorCranks]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[102]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[36.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/y/905/Seight-FlexorCranks_Arm_Warmers_CHROME_210212__70245_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.3900 cm]]></g:width>
	<g:shipping><g:price><![CDATA[0]]></g:price></g:shipping>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[FlexorCranks Short Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/flexorcranks-short-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Are you looking for a comfy, reliable, superior quality jersey at an economical price? Then the Seight Short Sleeve Jersey is what to go for. Made from pure 100% polyester, and designed with specially engineered quick drying micro fibres, it&amp;rsquo;s your optimum solution when it comes to wicking moisture from the body and keeping you cool. Its fabric is UV rated, protecting you form the sun&#039;s harmful rays.  The jersey comes standard with a 3/4 length zipper for regulating air flow when you&amp;rsquo;re riding. It also has a waist gripper that holds the edge of your jersey from rising above your waist, and three pockets to hold cycling accessories.   &amp;nbsp;  This jersey is available in these types:  &amp;bull; Men&#039;s Club and Casual Cut  &amp;bull; Women&#039;s Club Cut]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[FlexorCranks]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[103]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[70.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/a/658/Seight-FlexorCranks_Short_Sleeve_Jersey_CHROME_210212__45081_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:shipping><g:price><![CDATA[0]]></g:price></g:shipping>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[FlexorCranks Water Resistant Vest]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/flexorcranks-water-resistant-vest]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[When the weather is at its worst, our Water Resistant Vest is at its best. They are made from wind and water resistant polyester fabrics to enhance comfort and performance when you are riding. This vest is lightweight and breathable for an outstanding cycling experience. It has a mesh back or sides that regulates temperature for max comfort.  These vests are amazingly packable, so they can be easily stashed into the rear pockets when the sun peaks out again. These vests come in handy during those freakish weather conditions that may change from sun to rain in a heart bit.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[FlexorCranks]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[104]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[70.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/j/404/Seight-FlexorCranks_Vest_CHROME_210212__08793_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.1400 cm]]></g:width>
	<g:shipping><g:price><![CDATA[0]]></g:price></g:shipping>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Adelaide Casual Winter Vest]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/adelaide-casual-winter-vest]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[This casual winter vest will provide a great fit, it&amp;rsquo;s made of a multi layer wind repellent membrane with 350 gsm thermal, windproof and waterproof fleeced fabric. The stand-up collar prevents chaffing and offers the desired comfort.  The vest is elegantly stitched to eliminate binding and pinching, giving you the ultimate wear comfort. It&amp;rsquo;s completed with pockets in the front to keep your hands nice and warm. High definition graphics keep it very much on trend and give it an eye-catching appearance.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Adelaide Cyclists]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[105]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[105.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/u/989/Seight_Casual_Winter_Vest__00629_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[2.1800 cm]]></g:width>
	<g:shipping><g:price><![CDATA[0]]></g:price></g:shipping>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Breeze Standard Short Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/breeze-standard-short-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Are you  looking for a comfy, reliable, and superior quality jersey at an  economical price? Then the Seight Short Sleeve Jersey is what you need.  Made from pure polyester, and designed with specially engineered quick  drying micro fibre, it&#039;s your optimum solution when it comes to wicking  moisture from the body and keeping you cool.  The  jerseys fabric is UV rated, protecting you from the sun&#039;s harmful rays.  It comes standard with a 3/4 length zipper for regulating air flow when  you&#039;re riding, and also has a waist gripper that holds the edge of your  jersey from rising above your waist. For those who like to carry  multiple items, its 3 pockets will allow you to hold all your cycling  accessories.  Features  - Club and Relaxed Cuts- 3/4 length zipper-Super Light weight- 145 gsm UPF25+ fabric- 3 rear pockets ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Breeze]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[108]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[79.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/h/070/Seight_Jersey_Chrome_-_Breeze_120712__13162_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:shipping><g:price><![CDATA[0]]></g:price></g:shipping>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Breeze Elite Long Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/breeze-elite-long-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Nothing provides you with protection and comfort when you are out for a ride like the Seight Elite Long Sleeve Jersey. Its wide surface area removes moisture from your body quickly to protect your skin against bacterial infections and odour. The high tech fibre fabric ensures complete air circulation for a cool and dry body.The jersey is UV rated to protect your skin and the jersey from the harmful radiation from the sun. Its breathable panels are made from 2 stretchable fabrics to ensure comfort and maximum movement ability, while remaining lightweight and fast drying. It has three rear pockets located on its back to carry heavy cycling accessories, and the full length zipper comes in handy when venting heat.      Features  - UV protective fabric- Naturally soft, lightweight, stretchable and breathable- 145 gsm UPF 50+ fabric- YKK zipper        ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Breeze]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[109]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[113.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/x/051/Seight_Long_Sleeve_Jersey_Chrome_-_Breeze_120712__82814_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:shipping><g:price><![CDATA[0]]></g:price></g:shipping>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Breeze  Elite Short Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/breeze-elite-short-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Outstanding performance, perfect fit, and comfort, ride like a pro in our Elite Short Sleeve Jersey. Its high performance fabrics perform brilliantly in wicking moisture from the body. Its fabric is UV rated, protecting you form the sun&#039;s harmful rays.  Offering a soft and silky feel, it&amp;rsquo;s made up of two lightweight, stretchable, and breathable fabrics on different panels of the garments. It has three rear pockets which give you easy access to your riding essentials. The full zipper allows the flow of air, giving you the comfort and fresh air needed throughout your ride. It has a silicon waist gripper that ensures the hem does not &amp;lsquo;ride up&amp;rsquo; leaving your waist exposed when cycling.   This jersey comes in the following varieties:  &amp;bull; Men&amp;rsquo;s Pro Race, Club and Casual Cut  &amp;bull; Women&amp;rsquo;s Pro Race and Club Cut]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Breeze]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[110]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[102.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/g/000/Seight_Jersey_Chrome_-_Breeze_120712__49781_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:shipping><g:price><![CDATA[0]]></g:price></g:shipping>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Breeeze Winter Arm Warmers]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/breeeze-winter-arm-warmers]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Transform all your short sleeve  cycling jerseys into full body coverage with our Seight Winter Arm  Warmers. These arm warmers are made using full motion flexible fabrics,  fleece lining and elastic grippers that equipe you for those cold rides.  They are anatomically shaped to  enhance comfort and flexibility when you are on the saddle. Its silicon  made grippers are very durable and act brilliantly in preventing the arm  warmers from sliding down. They are digital printed to provide a long  lasting and high definition fabric.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Breeze]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[113]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[36.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/p/002/Seight_ArmWarmers_Chrome_-_Breeze_120712__59038_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.3900 cm]]></g:width>
	<g:shipping><g:price><![CDATA[0]]></g:price></g:shipping>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Breeze Tech Polo Shirt]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/breeze-tech-polo-shirt]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[You will in no doubt fall in love with our intricately designed polyester Seight Tech polo shirt. Made using a fast wicking fabric, it&amp;rsquo;s resilient to odour causing bacteria and allows moisture management. The fabric feels good to the skin, making it a relaxed, comfortable fit. It can be customized as per individual specifications.   Th whole shirt can be fully sublimated with images, logos or designs of your choice. Creative distinct artwork is done exclusively on every polo shirt and every size for high definition prints. It has the choice of a front zipper or 3 buttons on the front, with excellent prices on both. This jersey has a high tear strength that guarantees you the value of your money.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Breeze]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[114]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[54.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/r/013/Seight_Polo_-_Breeze_120912__54249_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[2.0400 cm]]></g:width>
	<g:shipping><g:price><![CDATA[0]]></g:price></g:shipping>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[ Breeze Elite Bib Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/breeze-elite-bib-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Are you a looking for a super comfortable pair of bib shorts? Then our Seight Elite Bib Shorts is what you should think of. It&amp;rsquo;s made of polyester and lycra fabrics to ensure greater flexibility. Its flatlock style stitching ensures gentle seams resultingine less discomfort. The multipanel design enables it to fit perfectly when you bend over in a cycling posture, while the silicon made leg grippers hold your shorts from riding up during pedalling.  The seamless super high-tech chamois is made in a way that decreases friction between your body and the saddle to increases comfort. The 3 multi structure levels relieve the pressure points between your body and your bike saddle. The fabrics and forms are anatomically combined to support your body and reduce muscle fatigue. These chamois features are what help makeour bib shorts the most comfortable all over Australia.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Breeze]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[115]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[131.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/u/740/Seight_Bib_Shorts_Chrome_-_Breeze_120712__83411_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.3900 cm]]></g:width>
	<g:shipping><g:price><![CDATA[0]]></g:price></g:shipping>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[ Breeze Elite Pro Bib Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/breeze-elite-pro-bib-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Perfect, immaculate, and incredible - is what best describes the Seight Elite Bib Shorts. It is indeed the top pro bib shorts ever made, bar none! The sublimated panel is made with 240gsm Lycra from Italy, while the unsublimated panel is 225gsm, which means maximum quality and breathability during extreme physical workouts.   The Italian made chamois has a number of features, such as being seamless, an anatomical shape, and multi-level structures for increased comfort and protection. Its elite thread Flatlock stitching method gives this short an appealing look and a soft feeling on the skin, and the power band leg gripper keeps the bib shorts in place.   Features  - Sublimated Panel: Italian LYCRA&amp;trade; 240 gsm  - Unsublimated Chamois Panel: Italian LYCRA&amp;trade; 225 gsm  - Elite 3D Italian Chamois  - Elite 6 thread FLATLOCK stitching- Power Band leg gripper]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Breeze]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[116]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[151.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/k/256/Seight_Bib_Shorts_Chrome_-_Breeze_120712__51743_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.4600 cm]]></g:width>
	<g:shipping><g:price><![CDATA[0]]></g:price></g:shipping>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[ Breeze Wind  Vest]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/breeze-wind-vest]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[When the weather is at its worst, our Water Resistant Vest is at its best. They are made from wind and water resistant polyester fabrics to enhance comfort and performance when you are riding. This vest is lightweight and breathable for an outstanding cycling experience. It has a mesh back or sides that regulates temperature for max comfort.  These vests are amazingly packable, so they can be easily stashed into the rear pockets when the sun peaks out again. These vests come in handy during those freakish weather conditions that may change from sun to rain in a heart bit.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Breeze]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[117]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[70.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/e/655/Seight_Vest_Chrome_-_Breeze_120712__36511_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.1400 cm]]></g:width>
	<g:shipping><g:price><![CDATA[0]]></g:price></g:shipping>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Breeze Standard Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/breeze-standard-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The Seight Breeze Shorts are  anatomically designed for the ultimate comfort whilst riding. Made with  multi-panelled Lycra,  these shorts are very breathable and leave no  room for bacteria propagation. It has a different density throughout the  chamois to give you comfort in all of your pedalling positions.   The waistband ensures  the shorts remain firmly in place at all times, and offers the ultimate  comfort and flexibility whether competing in a race or riding for  leisure.  Features  - Sublimated Panel: POLY-LYCRA&amp;trade; 220 gsm  - Unsublimated Chamois Panel: NYLON-LYCRA&amp;trade; 220 gsm  - Elastic Waistband- Silicon Gel Chamois - Elite 6 thread FLATLOCK stitching]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Breeze]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[118]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[94.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/j/612/Seight_Bib_Shorts__-_Breeze_012013__55862_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.1400 cm]]></g:width>
	<g:shipping><g:price><![CDATA[0]]></g:price></g:shipping>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Breeze Elite Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/breeze-elite-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Product Description    Thinking of high  performance, comfortable and yet durable cycling shorts? Look no further  than the Breeze Elite Shorts. This magnificent design is made using  Italian sublimated Miti Shield Lycra, which ensures good perspiration  absorption, and provides a healthy and comfortable ride. The pad has a  high varying density to provide you with comfort by acting as shock  absorbers in the perinea area.   The Elite Shorts are  anatomical shaped to give a perfect fit and an easy time through out the  ride. They are designed with 6 thread Flatlock stitching technology  that eliminates chafing, and feature an elastic and flexible waist band  which holds the shorts tightly in their position, and prevents body  exposure.   Features  - Sublimated Panel: POLY-LYCRA&amp;trade; 220 gsm  - Unsublimated Chamois Panel: NYLON-LYCRA&amp;trade; 220 gsm  - Elite 3D Italian Chamois    ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Breeze]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[119]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[112.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/e/605/Seight_Bib_Shorts__-_Breeze_012013__28357_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.1400 cm]]></g:width>
	<g:shipping><g:price><![CDATA[0]]></g:price></g:shipping>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel  Elite Pro Short Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/fixed-wheel-elite-pro-short-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Are you looking for cycling attire that is unique, elegant and classy? Then, don&amp;rsquo;t go further than the Seight Elite Pro Short Sleeve Jersey. Made from high quality Italian and USA fabrics, this should be the ultimate jersey for anyone that want that extra bit of quality.Like the Aero pro short sleeve jerysey  the power band sleeves heightens joint stability by improving muscle balance. T  With the jersey designed in a way that completely hugs the curves of your body, you will be confident and comfortable, while the seamless power band sleeves will ensure your biceps dont feel like they&#039;re being restricted. The full zipper allows good air ventilation and cools your body when it warms up, and you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be worried of your essentials as the three rear pockets will carry them safely.   Features  - Pro Race and Club Cuts- Full length zipper- Seamless power band sleeves- Fabrics sourced from both Italy and USA (3 different fabrics used on each jersey)- Mesh underams- 3 ...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[120]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[79.2000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/r/170/Seight_Jersey_Chrome_-_Fixed_Wheel_021713__19392_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel Elite Pro Bib Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/fixed-wheel-elite-pro-bib-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Perfect, immaculate, and incredible - is what best describes the Seight Elite Bib Shorts. It is indeed the top pro bib shorts ever made, bar none! The sublimated panel is made with 240gsm Lycra from Italy, while the unsublimated panel is 225gsm, which means maximum quality and breathability during extreme physical workouts.   The Italian made chamois has a number of features, such as being seamless, an anatomical shape, and multi-level structures for increased comfort and protection. Its elite thread Flatlock stitching method gives this short an appealing look and a soft feeling on the skin, and the power band leg gripper keeps the bib shorts in place.   Features  - Sublimated Panel: Italian LYCRA&amp;trade; 240 gsm  - Unsublimated Chamois Panel: Italian LYCRA&amp;trade; 225 gsm  - Elite 3D Italian Chamois  - Elite 6 thread FLATLOCK stitching- Powe Band leg gripper]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[121]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[90.6000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/x/381/Seight_Bib_Shorts_Chrome_-_Fixed_Wheel_021713__11535_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.4600 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel Gloves]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/fixed-wheel-gloves]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Hyper ventilated, ultra-light and close fitting, our comfortable Seight Summer Gloves are all a pro rider needs to emerge victorious. They are made of highly breathable lycra fabric that is both light in weight and chaff-free for a cool and comfy feeling. The palm has the perfect contour for a tight fit on the handlebar and also acts as a shock absorber from the riding vibrations.The insulated polyester lycra contains highly absorbent microfibers for quick drying and effective moisture transfer.   This high performing glove has an excellent air ventilation system for maximum air flow. The anatomically shaped inner padding sets the gloves in the hands perfectly for ultimate support, while the optional velcro wrist closure ensures these Seight gloves have a secure fit. They are fully sublimated for durable and breathable High Definition prints. You can choose your preferred colours from our wide range of summer gloves varieties.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[122]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[24.6000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/b/966/Seight_Gloves_Chrome_-_Fixed_Wheel_021713__30320_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.6800 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel Cap]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/fixed-wheel-cap]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The Seight Cap is designed from a soft, lightweight, waterproof, wind repelling, and extremely breathable poly fabric. It has an exceptional ability to soak up sweat and prevent it from running into your eyes. It also dries quickly and its machine washable.  The cap is reinforced with a strong elastic fastener to hold it tightly in place when the wind whips past your ears. It fits under your helmet nicely for an amazing look and a relaxed ride. The cap is fully sublimated, meaning high quality durable prints, while giving you a wide array of different colors to choose from. For a cap only order, our Seight caps come in a package of 15 pieces minimum, and 10 pieces if they are part of a jersey order.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[123]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[14.4000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/g/624/Seight_Cycling_Cap_-_Fixed_Wheel_021713__49720_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.6100 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel Thermal Jacket]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/fixed-wheels-thermal-jacket]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Comfortable, warm, and economical; what else is there to look for in a cycling jacket.  The jackets fabric is water and wind resistant to keep you warm and provide moisture wicking for a warm and dry body. The jacket is made with 3 windproof fabric layers which incorporate Roubaix fleece, as well as a&amp;nbsp; large collar. It is stitched using a cover stitch technique for durable and elegant seams.   The jacket is equipped with a full windproof zipper for protection against the cold weather, while providing efficient air ventilation. It features an elastic gripper to prevent your jacket from flying up when cycling, and has 3 optional spacious rear pockets to stash your riding gear. It&amp;rsquo;s digitally printed to give long lasting and quality graphics. Seight thermal jacket has all it takes to beat the cold weather.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[124]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[105.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/u/251/Seight_Winter_Jacket_Chrome_-_Fixed_Wheel_021713__81911_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.3200 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel Leg Warmers]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/fixed-wheel-leg-warmers]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Increase your legs warmth while wearing your best cycling shorts. Seight Winter Leg Warmers uses high quality Roubaix fabrics for exceptional wind protection without excluding moisture management and breathability. They have a fleece lining to keep you warm during cold rides. They are anatomically shaped to enhance comfort and increase riding performance.  The durable elastic gripper ensures the warmer is tightly attached to your body, to minimize contact of the cold breeze with your skin and increase comfort. They are sublimated to guarantee quality graphics and breathable fabric.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[125]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[29.4000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/y/848/Seight_Leg_Warmers_-_Fixed_Wheel_021713__20549_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.4600 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel Arm Warmers]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/fixed-wheel-arm-warmers]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Transform all your short sleeve cycling jerseys into full body coverage with our Seight Winter Arm Warmers. These arm warmers are made using full motion flexible fabrics, fleece lining and elastic grippers that equipe you for those cold rides.  &amp;nbsp;They are anatomically shaped to enhance comfort and flexibility when you are on the saddle. Its silicon made grippers are very durable and act brilliantly in preventing the arm warmers from sliding down. They are digital printed to provide a long lasting and high definition fabric.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[126]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[21.6000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/u/609/Seight_Arm_Warmers_Chrome_-_Fixed_Wheel_021713__74699_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.3900 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel Wind Vest]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/fixed-wheel-windvest]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[When the climate is at its worst, the Seight Windt Vest is at its best. They are made from wind and water resistant polyester fabrics to enhance comfort and performance when you are riding. The vest is lightweight and breathable for an outstanding cycling experience, and has a mesh that regulates temperature for maximum comfort.  These vests are amazingly packable, so they can be easily scrunched into the rear pockets when the sun peaks out again. Its graphics are sublimated for high quality prints and keep the fabric breathable. They really come in handy during those freakish weather condition which always seem to change from sunshine to rain when you least expect it. ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[127]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[57.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/x/398/Seight_Vest_Chrome_-_Fixed_Wheel_021713__86428_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.1400 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Fixed Wheel Short Sleeve Seight Suit]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/fixed-wheel-short-sleeve-seight-suit]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Description is top secret! You will find out what its like when you get it!!]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Skinsuits]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[128]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[265.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/f/703/Seight_Short_Sleeve_Skin_Suit_-_Fixed_Wheel_021713__06463_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.9600 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria Winter Arm Warmers]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/cycling-victoria-winter-arm-warmers]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Transform all your short sleeve cycling jerseys into full body coverage with our Seight Winter Arm Warmers. These arm warmers are made using full motion flexible fabrics, fleece lining and elastic grippers that equipe you for those cold rides.  &amp;nbsp;They are anatomically shaped to enhance comfort and flexibility when you are on the saddle. Its silicon made grippers are very durable and act brilliantly in preventing the arm warmers from sliding down. They are digital printed to provide a long lasting and high definition fabric.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[129]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[36.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/x/765/Seight_Arm_Warmers_Chrome_-_Cycling_Victoria__49747_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.3900 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria Summer Gloves]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/cycling-victroia-summer-gloves]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Hyper ventilated, ultra-light and close fitting, our comfortable Seight Summer Gloves are all a pro rider needs to emerge victorious. They are made of highly breathable lycra fabric that is both light in weight and chaff-free for a cool and comfy feeling. The palm has the perfect contour for a tight fit on the handlebar and also acts as a shock absorber from the riding vibrations.The insulated polyester lycra contains highly absorbent microfibers for quick drying and effective moisture transfer.   This high performing glove has an excellent air ventilation system for maximum air flow. The anatomically shaped inner padding sets the gloves in the hands perfectly for ultimate support, while the optional velcro wrist closure ensures these Seight gloves have a secure fit. They are fully sublimated for durable and breathable High Definition prints. You can choose your preferred colours from our wide range of summer gloves varieties.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[130]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[41.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/h/350/Seight_Gloves_Chrome_-_Cycling_Victoria__43407_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.6800 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria Wind/Rain Jacket]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/cycling-victoria-windrain-jacket]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[With wind and water resistance, a sleek look and comfy feeling, our Seight Wind Jackets are specifically designed for high performance and protection from wet weather conditions.   This jacket is designed to fight wind, chilly air, and water when pedalling. It has optional zippered rear pockets to provide easy access to your riding accessories, and has a perfect contour to improve mobility in all cycling positions. This jacket is also made with a silicon waistband, so it wont ride up your body whilst cycling.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[131]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[82.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/d/518/Seight_Rain_Jacket_Chrome_-_Cycling_Victoria_021213__40650_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.2500 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria Winter Thermal Jacket]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/cycling-victoria-winter-thermal-jacket]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Comfortable, warm, and economical; what else is there to look for in a cycling jacket.  The jackets fabric is water and wind resistant to keep you warm and provide moisture wicking for a warm and dry body. The jacket is made with 3 windproof fabric layers which incorporate Roubaix fleece, as well as a large collar. It is stitched using a cover stitch technique for durable and elegant seams.   The jacket is equipped with a full windproof zipper for protection against the cold weather, while providing efficient air ventilation. It features an elastic gripper to prevent your jacket from flying up when cycling, and has 3 optional spacious rear pockets to stash your riding gear. It&amp;rsquo;s digitally printed to give long lasting and quality graphics. Seight thermal jacket has all it takes to beat the cold weather.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[132]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[175.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/i/261/Seight_Long_Sleeve_Jersey_Chrome_-_Cycling_Victoria_021213__21854_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.3200 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria Winter Long Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/cycling-victroia-winter-long-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[The Seight Winter Long Sleeve Jersey rises above its competitors when it comes to keeping you warm in the freezing cold of winter. Its wide surface area removes moisture from your body quickly to protect your skin against bacterial infections and odour, while the high-tech inner fleece shell works to keep your body warm and dry.   The jerseys breathable panels are made from stretchable fabrics to ensure comfort and maximum movement ability, while remaining lightweight and fast drying. It has three rear pockets located on its back to carry heavy cycling accessories, and the full length zipper comes in handy if you need to vent a bit of heat.  Features  - 280 gsm 100% polyester- Full length zipper- Designed with specially-engineered quick-drying microfiber; - Naturally soft, lightweight, stretchable, breathable and comfortable; - Sweat-expelling, odor and bacteria resistant;  - Keeps the wearer dry, cool and fresh.        ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[133]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[117.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/q/830/Seight_Long_Sleeve_Jersey_Chrome_-_Cycling_Victoria_021213__51266_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.2900 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria Wind Vest]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/cycling-victoria-wind-vest]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[When the climate is at its worst, the Seight wind vest is at its best. They are made from wind and water resistant polyester fabrics to enhance comfort and performance when you are riding. The vest is lightweight and breathable for an outstanding cycling experience, and has a mesh that regulates temperature for maximum comfort.  These vests are amazingly packable, so they can be easily scrunched into the rear pockets when the sun peaks out again. Its graphics are sublimated for high quality prints and keep the fabric breathable. They really come in handy during those freakish weather condition which always seem to change from sunshine to rain when you least expect it. ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[134]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[81.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/p/216/Seight_Vest_Chrome_-_Cycling_Victoria_021213__89888_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[1.1400 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria Elite Pro Short Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/cycling-victoria-pro-short-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Are you looking for cycling attire that is unique, elegant and classy? Then, don&amp;rsquo;t go further than the Seight Elite Pro Short Sleeve Jersey. Made from high quality Italian and USA fabrics, this should be the ultimate jersey for anyone that want that extra bit of quality. Like the Aero pro short sleeve jerysey  the power band sleeves heightens joint stability by improving muscle balance. T  With the jersey designed in a way that completely hugs the curves of your body, you will be confident and comfortable, while the seamless power band sleeves will ensure your biceps dont feel like they&#039;re being restricted. The full zipper allows good air ventilation and cools your body when it warms up, and you don&amp;rsquo;t have to be worried of your essentials as the three rear pockets will carry them safely.   Features  - Pro Race and Club Cuts- Full length zipper- Seamless power band sleeves- Fabrics sourced from both Italy and USA (3 different fabrics used on each jersey)- Mesh underams- 3...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[135]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[132.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/d/493/Seight_Jersey_Chrome_-_021213__00447_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria Elite Short Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/cycling-victoria-elite-short-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Outstanding performance, a perfect fit, and extreme comfort; ride like a pro in our Seight Elite Short Sleeve Jersey. Its high performance fabrics perform brilliantly in wicking moisture from the body, while it is also UV rated, protecting you form the sun&#039;s harmful rays. Offering a soft and silky feel, the jersey is made up of two lightweight, stretchable, and breathable fabrics on different panels of the garments.   The short sleeve jersey has three rear pockets which give you easy access to your riding essentials, and the full zipper allows the flow of air, giving you the comfort and fresh air needed throughout your ride. It also has a silicon waist gripper that ensures the hem does not &amp;lsquo;ride up&amp;rsquo; leaving your waist exposed when cycling.   Features  - Pro Race, Club and Relaxed Cuts- Full length zipper- &quot;Natural&quot; sleeves- 145 gsm UPF50+ fabrics- 3 rear pockets ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[136]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[102.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/h/033/Seight_Jersey_Chrome_-_021213__15689_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria Short Sleeve Jersey]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/cycling-victoriashort-sleeve-jersey]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Are you  looking for a comfy, reliable, and superior quality jersey at an  economical price? Then the Seight Short Sleeve Jersey is what you need.  Made from pure polyester, and designed with specially engineered quick  drying micro fibre, it&#039;s your optimum solution when it comes to wicking  moisture from the body and keeping you cool.  The  jerseys fabric is UV rated, protecting you from the sun&#039;s harmful rays.  It comes standard with a 3/4 length zipper for regulating air flow when  you&#039;re riding, and also has a waist gripper that holds the edge of your  jersey from rising above your waist. For those who like to carry  multiple items, its 3 pockets will allow you to hold all your cycling  accessories.  Features  - Club and Relaxed Cuts- 3/4 length zipper-Super Light weight- 145 gsm UPF25+ fabric- 3 rear pockets ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[137]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[79.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/w/958/Seight_Jersey_Chrome_-_021213__27502_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria Winter Elite Pro Bib Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/cycling-victoria-winter-elite-pro-bib-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[We refer to them as Seight Winter Elite Pro Bib Shorts, but you may call them the supreme comfort. Made from multi-panel fleece Lycra from Italy,  these custom bib shorts are very breathable and leave no room for bacteria propagation whilst keeping you warm on those early morning wintery rides. It has a different density throughout the chamois to give you comfort in all of your pedalling positions.  These elite winter bib shorts are made with a 6 thread Flatlock stitching technique for low profile seams to minimise the possibility of chafing, and giving a clean and smooth finish. The power band grippers ensure the bib shorts remain firmly in place at all times, and offers the ultimate comfort and flexibility whether competing in a race or riding for leisure.  Features  - Sublimated Panel: Italian Super Roubaix Gavia&amp;trade; 250 gsm  - Unsublimated Chamois Panel: Italian Super Roubaix Lombardia&amp;trade; 250 gsm  - Elite 3D Italian Chamois  - Elite 6 thread FLATLOCK stitching- Powe Band ...]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[138]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[155.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/f/161/Seight_Bib_Shorts_Chrome_-_Cycling_Victoria_021213__37732_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.4600 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria Bib Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/cycling-victoria-bib-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[If you are looking for a great entry-level bib shorts, the Seight Bib Shorts are exactly what you need. They are a modern and comfy cycling apparel that gives you great value for your money, and are well designed to fit both men and women riders, with specific patterns for each.  Standard stitching of these bib shorts ensures reduced sewing seams and a smooth feel, while the 6+ panel design conforms well to your body when you bend over in a cycling position. Made with a polyester and lycra sublimated panel, moisture wicking and breathability are enhanced to reduce the chances of chafing. The high density chamois lining is antibacterial, while the silicon leg gripper prevents the shorts from riding up.  &amp;nbsp;   ]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[139]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[94.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/g/059/Seight_Bib_Shorts_Chrome_-_Cycling_Victoria_021213__79252_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.3600 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria Elite Bib Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/cycling-victoria-elite-bib-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Are you a long distance rider? Then the Seight Elite Bib Shorts are perfect for you. They are made with high quality lycra fabrics to ensure breathability and enhanced comfort. Its Flatlock style stitching produces gentle seams resulting to smooth cycling, and the 8+ panels delivers a perfect fit when you bend over in a cycling posture.   The seamless super high-tech chamois is made in a way that decreases friction between your body and the saddle, and the silicon leg grippers hold the shorts in place for an increased level of comfort. The&amp;nbsp; multi structure levels relieve the pressure points between your body and your bike saddle, while the fabrics and foams are anatomically combined to support your body and reduce muscle fatigue. These chamois features make Seight Elite Bib Shorts the most comfortable cycling item available in Australia.]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[140]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[131.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/u/918/Seight_Bib_Shorts_Chrome_-_Cycling_Victoria_021213__92822_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.3900 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
<entry>
	<title><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria Elite Pro Bib Shorts]]></title>
	<link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-products/cycling-victoria-elite-pro-bib-shorts]]></link>
	<description><![CDATA[Perfect, immaculate, and incredible - is what best describes the Seight Elite Bib Shorts. It is indeed the top pro bib shorts ever made, bar none! The sublimated panel is made with 240gsm Lycra from Italy, while the unsublimated panel is 225gsm, which means maximum quality and breathability during extreme physical workouts.   The Italian made chamois has a number of features, such as being seamless, an anatomical shape, and multi-level structures for increased comfort and protection. Its elite thread Flatlock stitching method gives this short an appealing look and a soft feeling on the skin, and the power band leg gripper keeps the bib shorts in place.   Features  - Sublimated Panel: Italian LYCRA&amp;trade; 240 gsm  - Unsublimated Chamois Panel: Italian LYCRA&amp;trade; 225 gsm  - Elite 3D Italian Chamois  - Elite 6 thread FLATLOCK stitching- Powe Band leg gripper]]></description>
	<g:department><![CDATA[Cycling Victoria]]></g:department>
	<g:expiration_date><![CDATA[2013-04-30]]></g:expiration_date>
	<g:id><![CDATA[141]]></g:id>
	<g:condition><![CDATA[new]]></g:condition>
	<g:price><![CDATA[151.0000]]></g:price>
	<g:image_link><![CDATA[http://www.seightcustom.com.au/product_images/n/500/Seight_Bib_Shorts_Chrome_-_Cycling_Victoria_021213__21070_zoom.png]]></g:image_link>
	<g:weight><![CDATA[1.00 kg]]></g:weight>
	<g:width><![CDATA[0.4600 cm]]></g:width>
</entry>
</feed>