<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"  xmlns:isc="">
	<title type="html"><![CDATA[Seight Custom Cycling Wear: Latest News]]></title>
	<subtitle type="html"><![CDATA[The latest news from Seight Custom Cycling Wear.]]></subtitle>
	<link rel="self" href="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/rss.php?action=newblogs&amp;type=atom" />
	<id>http://www.seightcustom.com.au</id>
	<updated>2013-06-04T02:36:55Z</updated>
			<isc:store_title><![CDATA[Seight Custom Cycling Wear]]></isc:store_title>
	<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
		<published>2013-04-02T10:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2013-04-02T10:00:00Z</updated>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/57/2013-nrs-team-annoucement" />
		<id>http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/57/2013-nrs-team-annoucement</id>
		<title type="html" xml:space="preserve"><![CDATA[2013 NRS Team Annoucement]]></title>
		<content type="html" xml:space="preserve" xml:base="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/57/2013-nrs-team-annoucement"><![CDATA[<p>Australia&rsquo;s fastest growing custom cycling brand, Seight Custom  Cycling Wear, have joined forces with elite sports consulting firm The  Biomechanics, to form Seight Test Team p/b The Biomechanics, an exciting  new development team set to debut in this years 2013 National Road  Series.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.teamseight.cc/" target="_blank">Seight Test Team</a> p/b The Biomechanics are a Victorian based road  cycling team with a particular focus on the development of young riders  as both athletes and as individuals. Co-founders Tristan Wright and Luke  Postlethwaite have very deliberately structured the team with this in  mind, appointing mentors such as Nick Aitkin, Jay Bourke and new recruit  Ryan Obst (2011 Oceania Road Race Champion) to share valuable  experience with the younger riders.</p>
<p>These experienced heads should hold Seight Test Team p/b The  Biomechanics in good stead for an exciting and hopefully successful  first year in the NRS. Race Director Dean Berry has made his intentions  clear by setting the goal of a top 10 finish in this years overall NRS  standings. &ldquo;We are looking to finish somewhere inside the top 10 this  year and hopefully even progress to a Top 3 spot sometime in the near  future&rdquo;.</p>
<p><img class="__mce_add_custom__" title="seight-team-launch.jpg" src="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/uploads/seight-team-launch.jpg" alt="seight-team-launch.jpg" width="790" height="527" /></p>
<p>The team will be looking to make a strong start to their 2013  campaign with a good showing in next months Tour de Perth. The 4-day  stage race will take place from the 11th-14th of April and promises to  provide valuable experience at the very least for some of the team&rsquo;s  younger athletes.</p>
<p>One of the youngsters to look out for is 16-year-old Jordan Stannus  who has made an impressive start to his young cycling career by winning  the Points Race at last year&rsquo;s Pacific Youth Track Championships in  Taiwan.</p>
<p>In conjunction with the launch of Seight Test Team&rsquo;s new website,  www.teamseight.cc, there will be exclusive behind the scenes content  from the races and training rides released regularly via the team&rsquo;s <a href="https://www.facebook.com/TeamSeight" target="_blank"> Facebook page</a> and YouTube channel.</p>]]></content>
		<draft xmlns="http://purl.org/atom-blog/ns#">false</draft>
	</entry>
	<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
		<published>2013-01-25T10:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2013-01-25T10:00:00Z</updated>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/56/seight-girls-january-racing-round-up" />
		<id>http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/56/seight-girls-january-racing-round-up</id>
		<title type="html" xml:space="preserve"><![CDATA[Seight Girl's January Racing Round-Up]]></title>
		<content type="html" xml:space="preserve" xml:base="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/56/seight-girls-january-racing-round-up"><![CDATA[<p><img class="__mce_add_custom__" style="float: left; margin-right: 20px;" title="seighttrack1.jpg" src="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/uploads/seighttrack1.jpg" alt="seighttrack1.jpg" width="477" height="477" />Behind the walls at the Victorian Junior Track Championships, our team of three Seight track cycling girls brought the crowd to their feet, as Madison Fitzgerald, Jamie Gooding and Chloe Baggs contested four titles up for grabs over the weekend. For Fitzgerald and Gooding, this was their first state championships, and not surprisingly they were a little nervous! The Vic State Team is selected based on results at this event, so they were feeling the pressure. The events were mainly sprinter orientated, which suited our main sprinter, Gooding, whilst Baggs and Fitzgerald were focused on enduro event; the individual pursuit.</p>
<p>The first event was the 500TT, Fitzgerald placed 9th with a time of 42.637, Gooding 6th 41.909. Baggs performed incredibly yet was pipped at the post, her time of 39.023 saw her miss the gold medal by 0.28 of a second.</p>
<p>After a short break the qualifying heats for the IP began. Gooding qualified 8th with 2.54.260, Fitzgerald 7th with 2.53.180 and Baggs came 1st in a time 2.41.653.  A short time later Chloe rode in the pink and blue to claim gold, whilst being the only rider in all categories to go faster in the final, by posting a time of 2.40.502 and take the win by over 3 seconds. It was an outstanding achievement and showcased flawless legs in arguably one of the best looking kits out there!</p>
<p>However, it didn&rsquo;t end there. After a good nights rest it was back to the track for the final 2 sprint events. In the flying 200 qualifiers Gooding was 8th fastest in a time of 14.195, and a big surprise for an enduro Baggs qualified easily fastest in a time of 12.737. Gooding placed 8th overall following the repackage, while Baggs won every sprint round to win gold.</p>
<p>As if the girls weren't tired enough, after a short break it was time for the Keirin heats. Both Baggs and Fitzgerald placed 1st and 2nd in their heats, then in the final Fitzgerald placed 5th and Baggs got the Gold.</p>
<p>All in all it was a fabulous weekend for all 3 girls. Baggs came away with three gold and a silver. Our other girls managed a stellar performance by coming away with lots of very respectable placings, PB's in all events and a wealth of experience. For their first junior track championships, these girls have the world as their oyster!</p>
<p>Onto other news, this month has been huge in the world of cycling. The boys and girls in blue have been out and about; winning, placing and having a laugh, whilst amazing the general public with their striking good looking tans showcased in Seight blue.</p>
<p>Sam de Riter has just completed Road Nationals, where not only did she TT like a little pink rocket and climb the mountains like she was born on them, but if that&rsquo;s not all she also came 15th overall in a very competitive field. Her results stand as; 15th in TT, 16th in Crit and 16th in RR. She is the most incredible girl, pushing all her boundaries and doing herself and all those around her proud. This weekend has also seen de Riter compete in the Vic Champs, making her mark on 2013! This chick has style, coming 3rd, and even though we may be slightly biased, she was most certainly the best looking up on the podium!</p>
<p>In other news these Seight chicks continue to dominate other events across the state, West has taken out wins at a number of St Kilda events, and Fitzgerald has taken out bronze in the Victorian 5km JW17 Scratch race at Moama.</p>
<p>My my girls, you sure have been busy! Keep up the km&rsquo;s and keeping getting those toots from all those admiring fans of yours out on the road!</p>
<p>xoxo Seight Girl</p>]]></content>
		<draft xmlns="http://purl.org/atom-blog/ns#">false</draft>
	</entry>
	<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
		<published>2012-12-19T10:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2012-12-19T10:00:00Z</updated>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/55/seight-womens-team-debut-at-cykel-events-womens-grand-prix" />
		<id>http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/55/seight-womens-team-debut-at-cykel-events-womens-grand-prix</id>
		<title type="html" xml:space="preserve"><![CDATA[Seight Women's Team Debut at Cykel Events Women's Grand Prix]]></title>
		<content type="html" xml:space="preserve" xml:base="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/55/seight-womens-team-debut-at-cykel-events-womens-grand-prix"><![CDATA[<p>The debut of Seight Custom Cycling Women's team was bound to be memorable, and as always Casey Fields lived up to its reputation of ferocious headwinds.<br /><br />Yet as the sun burst through the clouds, each girl, nine in total, burst out of the time trial gates, the first event of the morning. Yet it was not without its problems for leading cyclist Sam de Riter, riding a wheel far from true and catching the brake every 3 revolutions. Yet, in true Seight style, she pushed on, placing 11th, thinking if only&hellip; She was followed by the Hocking sisters, Hunter, Steele, West, Gooding and Baggs. <br /><br />Each girl flew around the first corner, the back straight proving the main problem with speeds averaging mid 30's. And as each girl sprinted the final straight, Gooding and Baggs showed the gathering crowd these girls' sprinting abilities.</p>
<p><br /><img class="__mce_add_custom__" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;" title="seight-girls.jpg" src="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/uploads/seight-girls.jpg" alt="seight-girls.jpg" width="750" height="500" /><br />For many of the team it was their first - of many - sponsored races. And placings indicated just what to expect from these girls in races to come - great results along with award winning smiles that indicate cycling is not only a sport to them, it's a passion. <br />Women's B was announced with the team consisting of West, Hocking (S), Gooding and Grieg-Towers, and with that they took to the field with a phenomenal spring start that gained the top 4 places in the field for much of the race. The loudspeaker sung the girls praise as time after time they lead the main field, West and Grieg-Towers keeping main pace, Hocking keeping Gooding safe for the first sprint. At the 25 min mark Gooding pulled out a fantastic sprint that lead us to being in the top 5. Later in the race Hocking made a break that was truly gutsy, yet she pulled back to the safety of her team mates. The race finished with Hocking leading the team home,, closely followed by West. All in all, the first crit sure led people to check out the girls sporting the pink and blue.<br /><br />Women's A begun shortly after, the team favourites including de Riter and Baggs showed they meant business as they put in the hard yards in the top 10, followed by Hunter, Steele and Hocking (A). The race was fast paced and cheering at the side line clearly showed people were interested in the Seight Team. <br />Unfortunately a crash early on consumed team rider Hunter, leading to a 20 min break where the girls regrouped. Back into the race the four women showed their strength, as lap after lap, they finished in the main bunch. The final sprint showed Baggs, followed closely by de Riter, finishing in the top 10. With Steele and Hocking finishing in the main bunch. <br /><br />For a first race, some never having met their team mates before, these girls pulled out the goods. The infectious smiles and good cooking has ensured these girls certainly have set a standard for emerging women's teams, and future results will show just how good they really are! <br /><br />xoxo Seight Girl</p>
<p><br /><img class="__mce_add_custom__" style="display: block; margin-left: auto; margin-right: auto;" title="seight-nails.jpg" src="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/uploads/seight-nails.jpg" alt="seight-nails.jpg" width="612" height="612" /></p>]]></content>
		<draft xmlns="http://purl.org/atom-blog/ns#">false</draft>
	</entry>
	<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
		<published>2012-12-12T10:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2012-12-12T10:00:00Z</updated>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/54/official-jersey-supplier-of-the-2012-13-womens-grand-prix" />
		<id>http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/54/official-jersey-supplier-of-the-2012-13-womens-grand-prix</id>
		<title type="html" xml:space="preserve"><![CDATA[Official Jersey Supplier of the 2012-13 Women's Grand Prix]]></title>
		<content type="html" xml:space="preserve" xml:base="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/54/official-jersey-supplier-of-the-2012-13-womens-grand-prix"><![CDATA[<p>Seight Custom Cycling Wear is the Official Jersey Supplier for the 2013 Women&rsquo;s Grand Prix. Organised by Cykel and sponsored by companies such as Red Star Coffee, the Women&rsquo;s Grand Prix is a series of criterium races for women only. The event is held over 4 rounds at the best criterium circuits in Victoria, with two rounds at Casey Fields, and individual rounds at Bendigo and Yarra Blvd.</p>
<p>It was created to provide women with a platform to compete in full length races, without playing second fiddle to the men in combined events. Women often have their races shortened or cancelled, prize money reduced, or recognition diminished, in order to accommodate the men. The Women&rsquo;s Grand Prix allows female riders to showcase the quality of women&rsquo;s racing, and perform in a headline event of their own.</p>
<p>Seight Custom Cycling Wear will be sponsoring the four different classification titles which are up for grabs. They consist of:</p>
<p><strong><span style="color: #007ac2;">General Classification</span></strong></p>
<p>The Leader of the General Classification is awarded this jersey to be worn in the following round. If the rider is not available, the jersey will be worn by the next best placed rider.</p>
<p><strong><span style="color: #007ac2;">COATES HIRE&nbsp;Laps Leader Classification</span></strong></p>
<p>The leader of the COATES HIRE Laps Leader Classification is awarded this jersey to be worn in the following round. If the rider is not available or is the leader of the General Classification, the jersey will be worn by the next best placed rider.</p>
<p><strong><span style="color: #007ac2;">MYLAPS Prologue Classification</span></strong></p>
<p>The Leader of the MYLAPS Prologue Classification is awarded this jersey to be worn in the Prologue&nbsp;in the following round. If the rider is not available, or is the leader of the General Classification, the jersey will be worn by the next best placed rider.</p>
<p><strong><span style="color: #007ac2;">Novice Classification</span></strong></p>
<p>The leader of the novice classification is awarded this jersey to be worn in the following round. If the rider is not available, or is selected to be promoted to the Grand Prix events, the jersey will be worn by the next best placed rider.</p>
<p><img class="__mce_add_custom__" title="womens-grand-prix-jerseys.jpg" src="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/uploads/womens-grand-prix-jerseys.jpg" alt="womens-grand-prix-jerseys.jpg" width="790" height="1100" /></p>
<p>After a hugely successful launch last season, this summer marks the second running of the event in Australia. Over 100 riders have currently registered for the event, and 9 of those riders are being entered by Seight and being spread across 2 teams - Seight Custom Ladies Team 1 &amp; 2. The following riders will be representing Seight throughout the series:</p>
<table border="0" width="931" height="106">
<tbody>
<tr>
<td><span class="usercontent">Samantha de Riter</span></td>
<td><span class="usercontent">Chloe Baggs</span></td>
<td><span class="usercontent">Melanie Hunter</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><span class="usercontent">Ashleigh Hocking</span></td>
<td><span class="usercontent">Nina Greig-Towers</span></td>
<td><span class="usercontent">Stacey Hocking</span></td>
</tr>
<tr>
<td><span class="usercontent">Alison West</span></td>
<td><span class="usercontent">Jaime Gooding</span></td>
<td><span class="usercontent">Brittany Steele</span></td>
</tr>
</tbody>
</table>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>We hope to see you down there supporting the girls, and best of luck to all riders in the 2012-13 Women's Grand Prix.</p>]]></content>
		<draft xmlns="http://purl.org/atom-blog/ns#">false</draft>
	</entry>
	<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
		<published>2012-11-01T10:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2012-11-01T10:00:00Z</updated>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/53/cycling-team-sponsorship-press-release" />
		<id>http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/53/cycling-team-sponsorship-press-release</id>
		<title type="html" xml:space="preserve"><![CDATA[Cycling Team Sponsorship Press Release]]></title>
		<content type="html" xml:space="preserve" xml:base="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/53/cycling-team-sponsorship-press-release"><![CDATA[<p><span style="color: #0388c0;">Below is a copy of our recently published Press Release concerning our intended Sponsorship of Cycling Teams across Australia.</span></p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><span style="font-size: medium;"><strong>SPONSORSHIP AND SUPPORT AVAILABLE FOR CYCLING TEAM</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: medium;">In recognition of the support they have received from the cycling community in the past few years, Seight Custom Cycling Wear is looking to give back to the sport of cycling in Australia by offering a host of generous sponsorship packages to cycling teams and groups across the country.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: medium;">Seight are actively seeking both new and existing cycling teams to provide them with sponsorship and support through acting as the team&rsquo;s Official Clothing Supplier. They intend to sponsor teams in each state at NRS, state, club and group levels, so there are plenty of opportunities available for all teams within Australia.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: medium;">Selected teams can elect be fitted out entirely in premium Seight Custom Cycling Wear Kits, which offer a tremendous advantage over the regular cycling kit attire. All clothing items will be provided with substantial discounts, allowing riders to cycle in international standard kits at just a fraction of the price.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: medium;"><strong>ABOUT SEIGHT CUSTOM CYCLING WEAR</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: medium;">Seight Custom Cycling Wear is fast becoming one of Australia&rsquo;s most recognisable custom cycling wear brands, on the back of superior garment quality and competitive pricing. They have experienced a massive level of growth since their inception in 2010, and are on track to become of one the major players in the Australian market within the next couple of years.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: medium;">One of the main reasons for Seight&rsquo;s popularity is that they are able to provide European Professional Team level clothing, with its associated high performance and comfort levels, at a highly affordable price. Their cutting edge garment technology not only matches the quality of other Australian suppliers, but often beats them by a fair distance.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: medium;"><strong>SPONSORSHIP REQUIREMENTS</strong></span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: medium;">There are no restrictions on which cycling teams, clubs, or groups can apply for the Seight Sponsorship Package, although they do request that you uphold a high standard of ethics and behavior both on and off the track. Honesty and morals, good character and sportsmanship, clean riding and language, and respect for other riders and officials, are qualities which they feel embody the Seight image, and hence look for in applicants.</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: medium;">To request further information, or submit an application for sponsorship, please contact:</span></p>
<p><span style="font-size: medium;">Doug Wright, Director, Seight Custom Cycling Wear</span><br /><span style="font-size: medium;">1 Barina Rd, Glen Iris, VIC 3146</span><br /><span style="font-size: medium;">Office: (03) 9886 0214 Mobile: 0421 244 947</span><br /><span style="font-size: medium;">doug.wright@seightcustom.com.au</span><br /><span style="font-size: medium;">www.seightcustom.com.au</span></p>]]></content>
		<draft xmlns="http://purl.org/atom-blog/ns#">false</draft>
	</entry>
	<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
		<published>2012-10-17T16:43:53Z</published>
		<updated>2012-10-17T16:43:53Z</updated>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/52/official-jersey-supplier-of-the-2012-tour-of-the-goldfields" />
		<id>http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/52/official-jersey-supplier-of-the-2012-tour-of-the-goldfields</id>
		<title type="html" xml:space="preserve"><![CDATA[Official Jersey Supplier of the 2012 Tour of the Goldfields]]></title>
		<content type="html" xml:space="preserve" xml:base="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/52/official-jersey-supplier-of-the-2012-tour-of-the-goldfields"><![CDATA[<p>Seight Custom Cycling Wear is proud to be the Official Jersey Supplier of the 2012 NRS Tour of the Goldfields. The race leaders will be decked out in the Seight brand for the Overall Leader&rsquo;s yellow jersey, the Sprinter&rsquo;s green jersey, and the Queen of the Mountain pink jersey. We are looking forward to the coming event, and the start of a long and fruitful relationship with the NRS and the Tour of the Goldfields.</p>
<p>The inaugural Tour of the Goldfields is being held in Ballarat over the extended weekend from Friday the 19<sup>th</sup> to Sunday the 21<sup>st</sup> of October. It is the sixth and final event for women in the Subaru NRS, and the Ballarat Regional Tourism office have declared that they intend to provide a climatic and iconic deciding event in the NRS.</p>
<p>The event kicks off with the Victoria Park Criterium on Friday at 2:00pm, which is a 20 lap ride around a 2.1km circuit, with a sprint every 3 laps. Saturday sees both the 2<sup>nd</sup> and 3<sup>rd</sup> stages, which are the 20km Burrumbeet Team Time Trial at 11:00am, followed by the 58km Burrumbeet Road Race at 2:30pm. The Sunday finale is the Snake Valley Road Race at 11:00am. This is a 99km circuit with three intermediate sprints and six intermediate hill climbs.</p>
<p>A field of 53 women are expected to hit the streets of Ballarat for the Tour of the Goldfields, with nine of the top ten riders in this year&rsquo;s NRS scheduled to participate. Queensland&rsquo;s Ruth Corset holds an almost unassailable lead, after claiming victory in two of this year&rsquo;s five events, but Victoria&rsquo;s Lisa Jacobs still has a chance if she can also register her second NRS tour victory this season.</p>
<p>Corset leads the points standings on 670, with Jacobs back in second on 519 points. It will require an almost flawless performance from Jacobs in the Tour of the Goldfields to claim the 2012 NRS title from Corset. The third place battle is a much closer affair, with Victorian Miranda Griffiths holding a slight edge over Canberra&rsquo;s Rebecca Wiasak. A number of other riders remain in contention for placings, and it should be an exciting event.</p>
<p><img class="__mce_add_custom__" style="vertical-align: middle;" title="tour-of-the-goldfields.jpg" src="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/uploads/tour-of-the-goldfields.jpg" alt="tour-of-the-goldfields.jpg" width="790" height="351" /></p>]]></content>
		<draft xmlns="http://purl.org/atom-blog/ns#">false</draft>
	</entry>
	<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
		<published>2012-10-17T16:37:34Z</published>
		<updated>2012-10-17T16:37:34Z</updated>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/51/prizes-galore-at-the-go-bike-expo" />
		<id>http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/51/prizes-galore-at-the-go-bike-expo</id>
		<title type="html" xml:space="preserve"><![CDATA[Prizes Galore at the GO Bike Expo]]></title>
		<content type="html" xml:space="preserve" xml:base="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/51/prizes-galore-at-the-go-bike-expo"><![CDATA[<p>Seight Custom Cycling Wear will be featuring our cycling clothing and designs at the 2012 GO Bike Expo. It is being held at Melbourne&rsquo;s beautiful Alexandra Gardens from Friday the 19<sup>th</sup> of October to Sunday the 21<sup>st</sup> of October.</p>
<p>The GO Bike Expo is more than just a regular expo, and presents consumers and retailers with the hottest gear related to bikes. It is specifically tailored to the needs of bike and product retailers, and provides an event to showcase the latest and greatest cycling gear on the market.</p>
<p>It is held in conjunction with the Bupa Around the Bay in a Day event, which is Australia&rsquo;s largest mass-participation cycling event, which starts and finishes in Alexandra Gardens. An innovative new site layout has been incorporated to maximise visibility at the finish line, which will enable the 18,000 expected riders and 25,000 visitors to have greater access to the Expo.</p>
<p>While enjoying the fun and entertainment provided at the GO Bike Expo, don&rsquo;t forget to pop in and see us at the Seight Custom Cycling Wear stall. We have a heap of prizes and giveaways during the event, and you will also get to learn more about the technology behind our state-of-the-art custom clothing, and meet the riders from the Seight Cycling Team.</p>
<p>The big prize everyone will want to win is the $1,000 discount voucher on our custom cycling products. We also have $650 and $500 prizes, and 10 personalised cycling jerseys which can be won. In addition to that, there will be a sensational offer revealed at the event, so remember to ask for directions to stall 28 and come see Seight Custom Cycling Wear at the GO Bike Expo.</p>
<p><img class="__mce_add_custom__" style="vertical-align: middle;" title="go-bike-expo.jpg" src="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/uploads/go-bike-expo.jpg" alt="go-bike-expo.jpg" width="790" height="557" /></p>]]></content>
		<draft xmlns="http://purl.org/atom-blog/ns#">false</draft>
	</entry>
	<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
		<published>2012-10-04T10:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2012-10-04T10:00:00Z</updated>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/50/black-elefant-next-ride-best-ride" />
		<id>http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/50/black-elefant-next-ride-best-ride</id>
		<title type="html" xml:space="preserve"><![CDATA[Black Elefant - Next Ride, Best Ride]]></title>
		<content type="html" xml:space="preserve" xml:base="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/50/black-elefant-next-ride-best-ride"><![CDATA[<p>Seight Custom Cycling Wear recently partnered with Black Elefant to produce a state-of-the-art custom cycling kit for their rides and promotional activities. The intention was to create a visually appealing, performance driven cycling kit, which is made from selected high quality fabrics.</p>
<p>Black Elefant have been wearing the jerseys during recreational rides, organised events, as well as in races. Their riders have remarked that the comfort and feel has been tremendous, and there has also been positive feedback regarding the look and <a href="http://www.blackelefant.com.au/_blog/Black_Elefant_Blog" target="_blank">jersey design</a>.</p>
<p><img class="__mce_add_custom__" title="black-elefant-combo.jpg" src="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/uploads/black-elefant-combo.jpg" alt="black-elefant-combo.jpg" width="790" height="592" /></p>
<p>Additional photos of the Black Elefant kit can be found in the <a href="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/custom-cycling-clothing/Gallery?gallery_id=15">Happy Customers</a> section on our Gallery page. Overall, the team at Black Elefant have been extremely happy with their kits, and we are proud to have them amongst our growing list of Happy Customers.</p>
<p>Just in case you are wondering, no we have not been spelling Elefant wrong. The team at Black Elefant have always had a strong affinity with elephants after several real life encounters, and find they inspire a sense of direction, focus and strength in their business. The spelling with an F was done to represent family, friends, fun and fitness.</p>
<p>Black Elefant design and provide expertly crafted cycling related apparel and accessories, and are based in the Eastern suburbs of Melbourne. They have a strong focus on awareness and safety, and live to their motto of Next Ride, Best Ride. It&rsquo;s not all about being on the bike either, as they stock a range of organic cotton t-shirts to provide their customers with the same adrenalin rush as when they ride.</p>
<p><a href="http://www.blackelefant.com.au" target="_blank">www.blackelefant.com.au</a>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; <a href="https://twitter.com/_BlackElefant" target="_blank">Twitter</a>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; <a href="http://www.facebook.com/pages/Black-Elefant/354836984558158" target="_blank">Facebook</a>&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp; <a href="mailto:info@blackelefant.com.au">info@blackelefant.com.au</a></p>]]></content>
		<draft xmlns="http://purl.org/atom-blog/ns#">false</draft>
	</entry>
	<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
		<published>2012-09-01T10:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2012-09-01T10:00:00Z</updated>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/44/wade-edwards-wins-the-2012-sam-miranda-handicap" />
		<id>http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/44/wade-edwards-wins-the-2012-sam-miranda-handicap</id>
		<title type="html" xml:space="preserve"><![CDATA[Wade Edwards Wins the 2012 Sam Miranda Handicap]]></title>
		<content type="html" xml:space="preserve" xml:base="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/44/wade-edwards-wins-the-2012-sam-miranda-handicap"><![CDATA[<p><img class="__mce_add_custom__" style="float: left; margin-right: 20px;" title="wade-edwards-wins-2012-sam-miranda-handicap.jpg" src="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/uploads/wade-edwards-wins-2012-sam-miranda-handicap.jpg" alt="wade-edwards-wins-2012-sam-miranda-handicap.jpg" width="400" />Wade Edwards from the Seight Custom Cycling Wear Team won the 2012 Sam Miranda Handicap in a truly exciting finish. In a calculated maneuver, Edwards came from behind and edged into the lead at the last second, crossing the finish line just 0.025 seconds in front of Jarrod Moroni.</p>
<p>Wade Edwards rode in the 6 minute bunch, with other groups being given a 10, 15, 19 and 24 minute lead over the scratch group. The Sam Miranda handicap was over a total distance of 85km, and the 10 minute bunch was quickly collected by the 6 minute bunch at the 30km mark. From there these two groups managed to overtake the other groups ahead of them, while maintaining their lead over the scratch bunch.</p>
<p>There were no less than 18 riders in contention when they rounded the final corner to contest the sprint. Jarrod Moroni looked like he had the win in the bag with a powerful final sprint, but a momentary lapse in concentration cost him the title. Believing he was well ahead, Moroni sat up early and coasted the final few metres, but he failed to see Edwards on his tail and he was overtaken at the last possible moment.</p>
<p>In other events on the Sam Miranda weekend, Andrew Ward crossed the line first in the Gran Fondo, with a time of 3:20:06. Miranda Griffiths was the first of 3 riders under the 3-hur mark when she took out the Women&rsquo;s Road Race in 2:56:18, while Rhys Pollock was also the first of 3 riders in the Men&rsquo;s Road Race who were under 2 &frac12; hours when he won in 2:29:37.</p>
<p>Video footage of the race courtey of 7 News can be found below. Please note the reporter incorrectly quoted Wade Edwards as being in the 18 minute pack, whereas he started with the 6 minute bunch.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p style="text-align: center;"><iframe src="http://www.youtube.com/embed/e-239ATwPww" width="640" height="360" frameborder="0"></iframe></p>]]></content>
		<draft xmlns="http://purl.org/atom-blog/ns#">false</draft>
	</entry>
	<entry xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
		<published>2012-08-13T10:00:00Z</published>
		<updated>2012-08-13T10:00:00Z</updated>
		<link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/39/youtube-channel-launched" />
		<id>http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/39/youtube-channel-launched</id>
		<title type="html" xml:space="preserve"><![CDATA[YouTube Channel Launched]]></title>
		<content type="html" xml:space="preserve" xml:base="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/news/39/youtube-channel-launched"><![CDATA[<p><img class="__mce_add_custom__" style="margin-right: 20px; float: left;" title="youtube.jpg" src="http://www.seightcustom.com.au/uploads/youtube.jpg" alt="youtube.jpg" width="300" height="212" />Seight Custom Cycling Wear is proud to announce we have launched our Youtube channel with our first videos over the weekend. In addition to the initial videos, we will be uploading new content frequently, and we trust you will find the various vids contain a nice blend of humour and information.</p>
<p>The Seight Youtube channel will feature informative videos of our products, mixed in with a combination of funny and interesting cycling clips. Make sure you check it out, and dont forget to subscribe to the channel to stay in touch and ensure you don't miss any of the latest vids.</p>
<p>The channel can be visited at <a href="http://www.youtube.com/SeightCustom" target="_blank">http://www.youtube.com/SeightCustom</a></p>]]></content>
		<draft xmlns="http://purl.org/atom-blog/ns#">false</draft>
	</entry>
</feed>
